<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<?mso-application progid="Word.Document"?>
<pkg:package xmlns:pkg="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/2006/xmlPackage">
  <pkg:part pkg:name="/_rels/.rels" pkg:contentType="application/vnd.openxmlformats-package.relationships+xml" pkg:padding="512">
    <pkg:xmlData>
      <Relationships xmlns="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/package/2006/relationships">
        <Relationship Id="rId3" Type="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships/extended-properties" Target="docProps/app.xml" />
        <Relationship Id="rId2" Type="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/package/2006/relationships/metadata/core-properties" Target="docProps/core.xml" />
        <Relationship Id="rId1" Type="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships/officeDocument" Target="word/document.xml" />
      </Relationships>
    </pkg:xmlData>
  </pkg:part>
  <pkg:part pkg:name="/word/document.xml" pkg:contentType="application/vnd.openxmlformats-officedocument.wordprocessingml.document.main+xml">
    <pkg:xmlData>
      <w:document xmlns:wpc="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingCanvas" xmlns:cx="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2014/chartex" xmlns:cx1="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2015/9/8/chartex" xmlns:cx2="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2015/10/21/chartex" xmlns:cx3="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2016/5/9/chartex" xmlns:cx4="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2016/5/10/chartex" xmlns:cx5="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2016/5/11/chartex" xmlns:cx6="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2016/5/12/chartex" xmlns:cx7="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2016/5/13/chartex" xmlns:cx8="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2016/5/14/chartex" xmlns:mc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/markup-compatibility/2006" xmlns:aink="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2016/ink" xmlns:am3d="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2017/model3d" xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" xmlns:oel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/2019/extlst" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:m="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/math" xmlns:v="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:vml" xmlns:wp14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:wp="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:w10="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:word" xmlns:w="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main" xmlns:w14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordml" xmlns:w15="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2012/wordml" xmlns:w16cex="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2018/wordml/cex" xmlns:w16cid="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2016/wordml/cid" xmlns:w16="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2018/wordml" xmlns:w16du="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2023/wordml/word16du" xmlns:w16sdtdh="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2020/wordml/sdtdatahash" xmlns:w16sdtfl="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2024/wordml/sdtformatlock" xmlns:w16se="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2015/wordml/symex" xmlns:wpg="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingGroup" xmlns:wpi="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingInk" xmlns:wne="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2006/wordml" xmlns:wps="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingShape" mc:Ignorable="w14 w15 w16se w16cid w16 w16cex w16sdtdh w16sdtfl w16du wp14">
        <w:body>
          <w:p w14:paraId="419D1C34" w14:textId="5F0BC4BD" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRPr="001A3759" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="001A3759">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>Chapter 2: Trust</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4CAABEE4" w14:textId="43698195" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"WHERE THE FUCK IS SHE?!"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4D6A0798" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa's voice tore through the office like a blade, sharp and staunch, sending shockwaves down the corridor. Megumi stood frozen, hands clasped tightly in front of her, her knuckles white from the pressure. Her fingers trembled—just enough for Kurosawa to notice. His gaze snapped to her hands, then back to her face, eyes narrowing with suspicion. He rounded the desk with deliberate steps, each one echoing in the silence that had fallen around them.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="77B23918" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"You were there," he hissed, voice low and venomous. "You saw her. Don’t fucking lie to me!"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0B45369F" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"I—I didn’t see her!" Megumi stammered, her voice barely a whisper. Her eyes flickered to the side, searching for something—anything—to anchor her, before snapping back to meet his glare. "I swear, Kurosawa-san, I knocked… I waited. She didn’t answer."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="794D30A0" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa stepped forward, closing the distance between them, his shadow swallowing hers. His breath was hot, acrid with the scent of whiskey, his eyes burning holes through her composure. "And it didn’t cross your stupid little mind to call the fire department?! An ambulance?! The fucking police?! ME FOR CRYING OUT LOUD?!"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="214F532D" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>His voice thundered off the walls, reverberating through the silence, shaking her resolve. He had never shouted like this—not in the office, not in front of her. Megumi felt her knees threaten to buckle, the floor tilting beneath her. She forced herself to stand straight, spine rigid, hands still clasped in front of her, trembling just enough for him to see.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7B36B24C" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"I… no… it… I did not think…" Megumi stammered, her voice faltering under the weight of his gaze. Her hands twisted together, she did not know what to say, she could not come up with an excuse, and alibi fast enough, eyes widening with desperation. “I swear, I’m not—”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7C62FC5A" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>The door creaked open behind them, cutting her off. Kurosawa’s eyes snapped up, fury flashing across his features, but the expression halted—paused mid-ignition. Saito stepped in, his movements deliberate, unhurried, the echo of his shoes clicking softly against the polished floor.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7C77F484" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"Am I interrupting?" His voice was cool, smooth as glass, almost casual. He closed the door behind him with a soft click that seemed to reverberate in the silence. His eyes moved between Kurosawa and Megumi, lingering just long enough to register the tension crackling in the air.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="20EC547B" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa straightened, his gaze snapping to Saito. “Where the hell have you been?! Why weren’t you here yesterday?!”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="2571B526" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="163F2AB4" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito tilted his head slightly, his expression unreadable. “I always have Wednesdays off, Kurosawa-san. I was running errands. I didn’t realise there was a problem.” He glanced at Megumi, then back at Kurosawa. “What’s going on?”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="10560233" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa's nostrils flared, his fingers drumming impatiently on the desk. “This one here”— he jabbed a finger toward Megumi— “says she didn’t see Miku yesterday. Funny thing is, I know they were supposed to be at that fucking Hello! Interview, but she didn’t show up!”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4E9F2AF4" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito’s eyes flicked back to Megumi, and for just a second, something flashed behind his gaze—recognition, perhaps. His expression remained calm, almost surgical. “That’s not true,” he said, voice steady. “I saw you there, Nakayama-san. You and I were both at her flat, remember? I even made Miku-san some breakfast.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4B3FB6F8" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Megumi’s face drained of colour. Her mouth opened, then closed again, lips trembling as if the right words were locked behind her teeth. “I—I mean, yes, but she wasn’t well,” she corrected, voice barely above a whisper. Her gaze flicked nervously between Kurosawa and Saito, seeking refuge in neither. “I—I didn’t want to bother Kurosawa-san, she wasn’t feeling well, and…”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="665B2A3F" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“And you lied to me,” Kurosawa snarled, his voice laced with venom. He took a deliberate step forward, his eyes narrowing to vicious slits burned through her soul. “You were covering for her. What the fuck did you do!?”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="5270B124" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Megumi recoiled, her back pressing against the wall. “I didn’t do anything!” The words came out in a broken wail, her voice cracking under the weight of it. Her hands shook harder, fingers curling into fists at her sides, her whole body vibrating with fear. Tears slipped down her cheeks, unbidden and unrestrained, carving lines through her makeup. “I just… I didn’t want you to be angry, Kurosawa-san!”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="48488E64" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa scoffed, turning his attention back to Saito. “And you?”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="228B63C7" w14:textId="69533895" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">Saito’s expression remained placid, unbothered. “Like I said, I was just getting Miku-san’s breakfast. She asked for eggs and rice, so I made it, left it on the counter, and stepped out to take a call. When I came back, Nakayama-san was already there. We told her Miku-san </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00E712A6">
              <w:t>was not</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> feeling well, and I even suggested she take the day off since Miku-san planned to as well.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="587F8DC7" w14:textId="1A11E0C1" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">Kurosawa’s gaze shot back to </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00A33EAD">
              <w:t>Megumi’s</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>, his eyes searing through her composure. The lie had been exposed.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="306EE5E2" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Her lips trembled, eyes shimmering with barely contained fear. “I—I’m sorry… I just thought…”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="2975D9BB" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>“Thought what?” he snarled, his voice dripping with venom. “That I wouldn’t find out? That I wouldn’t come down on you like a hammer for trying to pull this shit?!”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="292EB17A" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">Megumi’s shoulders shrank inward, her head bowed. She was crushed under the weight of his rage, head bowed beneath the crushing weight of his fury. Saito watched in stillness, his expression unreadable. Though guilt twisted in his gut, he remained composed, hands folded neatly before him. Sacrifices had to be made, and her emotional fragility was collateral for a greater purpose. </w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7F5B674A" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“Get the fuck out,” Kurosawa growled, voice low and dangerous. Megumi flinched, then scurried out of the room, the door clicking shut behind her.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="70967725" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Silence settled thickly between them. Kurosawa brought his hands to his temples, rubbing slow, deliberate circles as if trying to exorcise a growing migraine. “What the hell is happening?”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="5765AA9F" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito didn’t respond right away. He waited, patient, watching Kurosawa with the calm of a man who knew exactly what was coming next. He needed to show he was the methodical and calculating partner.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="724F6A0E" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa’s hands fell to his sides, eyes bloodshot and seething with rage. “I don’t give a damn what you have lined up today—accounts can wait. Find her. NOW!”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6BA4822F" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito inclined his head in a subtle nod. “Of course, Kurosawa-san.” He turned to leave, hand resting on the door handle, but Kurosawa's voice cut through the silence.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="212342E2" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“Wait.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="60C98AAD" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He paused, glancing back over his shoulder.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="2ED9FFFE" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa's eyes were sharp, almost manic, but beneath the fury, there was something else—a flicker of doubt. “You’re sure you left her there? She was fine when you left?”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7C3E7163" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito’s smile was soft, almost disarming. “Of course. I made sure she was fine. Even brewed her some of that detox tea she likes—you know, after all those calories from the eggs. We have to keep our girl perfect.” He bowed slightly, the gesture smooth and deliberate. “I’ll bring her back, sir.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0290D310" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa didn’t respond, merely waved him off as he strode toward the whisky trolley. Saito stepped out, closing the door with a soft, deliberate click.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="08FDB61A" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Silence reclaimed the room, thick and suffocating. Kurosawa’s hands trembled—just enough to make his jaw clench. He yanked open the drawer, pulling out a crystal glass, then reached for a decanter of Hibiki 21. The amber liquid splashed into the glass, unceremonious and unmeasured. He took a long, burning sip, feeling the heat claw its way down his throat, then poured another.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="083FBA26" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>His gaze drifted to the corner of his desk, where a stack of papers lay untouched. The top sheet was immaculate, printed on heavy stock—its weight almost foreign to his hand as he picked it up.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0FD4FED8" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="79414DC7" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Sabbatical Request Form - Approved</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="5951D622" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>His eyes scanned the text, disbelief etching itself into his features. Her name was printed neatly at the top, followed by the dates of her intended leave, signed in delicate, familiar strokes.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3390C685" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa’s grip tightened around the glass, its surface groaning under the pressure of his fist. He read the form again, the letters blurring and swimming as his mind struggled to make sense of it. This wasn’t right. He hadn’t approved this. He would never have approved this.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="541CB2EF" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>The paper crumpled in his grasp, crushed into a jagged ball. His vision wavered; the room seemed to tilt, spiralling around him. He set the whisky down with a trembling hand, breaths coming sharp and shallow.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6C0953C3" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“What the fuck are you…?” he whispered into the empty room, the silence suffocating, pressing in on all sides.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3CDF50FB" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa's mind raced, the whisky glass trembling slightly in his grip. Eggs. The word repeated in his mind, echoing with a dull thud. Who the fuck craves eggs? It wasn't just breakfast. It wasn't just some simple meal Saito whipped up for her. It was a craving. A fucking pregnancy craving.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="5E3291D0" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>His jaw tightened, the tendons standing out sharply beneath his skin. “That little bitch…” he whispered, the words slipping out like venom. His gaze dropped to the crumpled sabbatical request still clenched in his fist. Slowly, he smoothed it out against the desk, fingers trembling with barely contained rage.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="5510B03A" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>A sabbatical. When? How? He had seen her every day—controlled her schedule, her diet, her every goddamn move. When the hell did she manage this? The signature stared back at him, elegant and deliberate. Hers. It was real.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7C458ED6" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“She didn’t take the goddamn pill…” he spat, the realisation crashing over him like a tidal wave. “She didn’t fucking take it!” His fist slammed onto the desk, the wood shuddering from the impact. The whisky glass tipped over, amber liquid spilling across the polished surface, bleeding into the edges of the paper. But it didn’t matter. Nothing mattered now. If she didn’t take the pill... if she’d lied…</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1385ABEB" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>His eyes flared with sudden understanding. The eggs. The breakfast. She’s pregnant. Hatsune Miku, his brightest star, his most prized possession. And she’s run off with HIS child.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0A2119BC" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>“No…” The word slipped out, barely a whisper, before he shot to his feet, the chair scraping harshly against the floor. “No fucking way.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="32E50017" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He paced the room, fingers raking through his hair, adrenaline coursing through his veins like wildfire. It wasn’t just that she was pregnant—he could have fixed that, handled it, just as he always did. No, this was something else. This was planned. A sabbatical. The timing was too precise to be coincidence.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="16412E14" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“She’s going to blackmail me,” he whispered, the words brittle and sharp, cracking the silence. His hands gripped the back of the chair, knuckles blanching under the pressure. “She’s going to have the damn kid, and she’ll ruin me! I’m the father… and she can prove it!”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="5D915FD3" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>His mind spiralled, linking fabricated dots with brutal precision. The timing. The cravings. The sabbatical. She’d orchestrated this—she had to have. Slipped the pill down the drain, faked every goddamn step, and now she was gone—vanished to have his child and drag his name through the mud.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="2D160216" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"That little bitch," he repeated snarling, voice cracking under the strain. His hand came down hard on the desk, the sharp sting radiating up his arm, grounding him in the chaos. His breathing grew ragged, shallow.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="405AD711" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“Where the fuck is she, Saito?!” he roared into the emptiness of his office, the walls swallowing his fury.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="77F96F2E" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>His eyes narrowed, the pieces falling together. Saito had been there. Saito had been in her flat— making her breakfast, feeding her, talking with her.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="372B26E8" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“Saito…” he whispered, the name curling off his tongue like a sour drink. He turned back to his desk, fingers dancing across the surface until he found his phone. The screen lit up with a glow that felt almost sickly. He dialled with shaking hands, the ringing pulsing in his ear.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0D805B0A" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“Shimada?” he barked the moment the line connected. The voice on the other end—his secretary—sputtered a greeting, but Kurosawa didn’t bother waiting.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1031506C" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“I need you to summon Takeguchi. Find him right now. I don’t give a shit what he’s doing—I want him in my office in five minutes. And get eyes on every fucking door, every goddamn security camera. Send someone to Hatsune Miku’s apartment building and bring me the goddamn footage by the end of the day!”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4EE70524" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He slammed the phone back into its cradle, the force rattling the desk. His hands shook as he gripped the edge, knuckles whitening as if he could hold the room still by sheer force of will. It felt too small—stifling. The walls seemed to close in, pressing against his ribs, squeezing the breath from his lungs.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0FBD21FA" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>His mind was a storm, thoughts colliding with vicious speed, each one screaming for dominance.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="65CD3CE0" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>The morning unravelled like a fraying thread, each moment tugging at the seams of her composure. Kurosawa's outburst still echoed in her mind—sharp, slicing, cutting through the professional façade she clung to. Now, Nakayama Megumi sat at her desk, hands trembling, Miku's fan letters scattered before her like the remnants of a collapsed tower. Her mobile phone lay silent—no messages, no calls—just the slow, relentless tightening of anxiety coiling in her chest.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0DA53B0A" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>A knock at the door shattered the fog of her thoughts. She straightened instinctively, smoothing her blouse with unsteady fingers. "Come in," she called, her voice taut and brittle.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="16D6A40F" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito stepped inside, his movements measured and composed. The door clicked shut behind him, the sound soft and deliberate. His gaze met hers—steady, almost unsettling in its familiarity. He inclined his head, polite but distant. "Nakayama-san," he greeted, his voice smooth and precise.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="43609A7B" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Her eyes flickered around the room, scanning for cameras, microphones—anything that might be watching, listening. "Saito-san," she replied, her tone guarded, the syllables clipped.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6C134203" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He advanced a step, hands resting neatly in his pockets. "I appreciate Kurosawa-san was… upset," he began, his gaze never wavering. "Understandably so. I thought I’d check on you."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="39D86B6B" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Her laugh was sharp and mirthless. "Check on me? Why would you care?". Saito arched an eyebrow. "Because you seem rattled, and that’s not like you," he replied plainly. He stepped closer, his voice dropping to a near whisper. "You’re smarter than that."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3E9DCB4D" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Megumi’s gaze flickered with uncertainty. "What do you mean?"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="468D243C" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He sighed, a slow exhale that seemed to drain the weight from his shoulders. "I’m not here to point fingers," he said softly. "I’m here to help you survive this."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="2FB3F4C7" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Her eyes widened, panic flaring behind them. "Survive what!? I didn’t bloody do anything…" she whispered, her voice trembling. "I just… I left her with you. She wasn’t feeling well. I thought she’d be fine…" The last word fractured, brittle and fragile.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="25C24E1C" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"And she will be," Saito assured her, his tone steady and measured. He leaned forward, resting his hands on her desk with deliberate calm. "But Kurosawa-san won’t see it that way. He’s not… understanding. You know that." His gaze sharpened, eyes piercing hers with quiet intensity. "If he believes she’s taken some time off… a sabbatical— it’s easier for everyone, don’t you think?"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="2A3B5D84" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>Megumi blinked, confusion etched in her features. "Sabbatical? She didn’t say anything about…"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7B6C0E01" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito nodded, his expression calm and resolute. "There’s a letter. Already filed and processed by HR this very morning," he explained smoothly. "Kurosawa saw the confirmation himself. It was handled by the morning staff. All… legitimate. All in order."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7B623764" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Her hands flew to her mouth. "But… I didn’t… she didn’t…"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="01F4016D" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"No," Saito agreed, his tone gentle yet unyielding. "But perhaps she felt she couldn’t. Perhaps she felt… stifled." He leaned back, his voice dropping to a near whisper. "Think about it. The workload, the appearances, the expectations. She was always perfect, wasn’t she?"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="08E75D16" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>His eyes locked onto hers, unflinching, searching. "When was the last time you saw her truly happy?"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="2EEAC819" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Megumi opened her mouth to answer, but the words died on her tongue. She couldn’t remember.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="000B2CE9" w14:textId="7D3BA565" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">Saito continued, his voice gentle yet </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="005A1901">
              <w:t>grounded</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>. "If she took a sabbatical, I think it’s in your best interest to say you knew about it. That you recognised she was overworked." His gaze was steady, calculated. "And I imagine the Performers’ Union would tear us apart if they found out how she’s been… managed."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="47C695F6" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He leaned back slightly, his posture relaxed, almost reassuring. "The best thing for everyone—for you, for Kurosawa—is to let her take a breath. He won’t come after you if you admit you were aware. I’m sure she’ll come back, don’t you think? She loves her fans."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="2873E01D" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito’s eyes flicked to the scattered fan letters on her desk. "She loves singing. She’ll be back. You know that. Just… let her take a breath."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="00698AF6" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Megumi blinked, her eyes glassy but resolute. "You think she’ll come back?"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6C04AB59" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="0A2E6714" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito’s smile was thin, almost paternal. "Of course," he replied smoothly. "This is her life—her fans, her music. She’s not running away; she’s just… stepping back from the stage for a moment. Even the brightest lights need a pause between acts."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="313521CA" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="5E5E0CB6" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Megumi’s brow furrowed, her fingers nervously twisting together. "But why would I admit to something that isn’t true? How does that help me?"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="591A8326" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">Saito took a measured step forward, his voice dropping to a whisper, soft and conspiratorial. "Because, Nakayama-san, if you don’t, Kurosawa will need someone to </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>blame. You know how he is—when things go wrong, someone always takes the fall." His gaze fixed on hers, unblinking. "And right now, his eyes are on you."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="69262B42" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Her breath hitched, the words sinking in.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="785676BD" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"But if you knew," he continued, voice silky and persuasive, "if you simply say that you saw the pressure, that you recognised she needed a reprieve… you become part of the solution, not the problem." He leaned back slightly, letting the idea settle. "Kurosawa’s anger isn’t really at you; it’s at the unknown. If you make it known, if you control the narrative, you’re not negligent—you’re considerate."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="281622DA" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He paused, allowing the silence to thicken. "And when she returns, you’ll be the one who understood. The one who protected her. Isn’t that better than being the one who missed all the signs?"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7443D823" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Megumi swallowed hard, her hands still shaking, but her expression softened—less guarded. Saito’s smile didn’t waver. "Just think about it," he said quietly. "It’s not a lie… it’s good sense."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="69C7B9D6" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Megumi repeated his words under her breath, as if the realisation had just settled in. "It is good sense…"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="2E314227" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito nodded, his expression softening with something almost like approval. "Exactly," he replied smoothly. "But for that to work, we need to let her step back. If Kurosawa-san starts barking up the wrong tree… making noise, it could become… problematic." His voice dipped, barely above a whisper. "For all of us."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="32C38BDD" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Megumi straightened, the tremor in her hands gone, replaced by a newfound resolve. "I understand," she said quietly, her tone steadier than before. "I’ll say I approved it… I’ll… I’ll let her step back."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="12D971E2" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito's smile was thin, but there was a flicker of genuine satisfaction beneath it. "I knew you would understand," he said smoothly. He straightened, brushing the wrinkles from his sleeves with deliberate care. "If Kurosawa-san asks, you were simply giving her space. She wasn’t feeling well, and you respected her privacy. You did nothing wrong, Nakayama-san. You were just… considerate. Nothing more."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3AF2A15A" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>His gaze lingered on her, steady and unyielding, as if willing the narrative into existence with every word.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0924C0A8" w14:textId="1D5BEEA4" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">Megumi nodded, relief softening the tension in her features. "Thank you, </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="009C32C9">
              <w:t>Takeguchi</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>-san," she murmured, her voice barely above a whisper.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="61FFA108" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="26D18BFF" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">Saito took a step back, his expression settling into its familiar mask of composure. "Of course. We look after our own," he replied, his tone smooth and assured. He turned and </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>exited her office, footsteps measured and deliberate, the door clicking shut behind him with a quiet finality.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4FF4722E" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>For the first time that day, Megumi exhaled—a long, unsteady breath that seemed to drain the weight from her shoulders.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6FCD1F8E" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="2B408A6A" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>As Saito stepped out of Megumi's office, he was met by Kurosawa's enforcers—a gang of four hulking brutes whose sole purpose was to ensure his word remained unchallenged. They moved as one, closing in around him like a tightening noose.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="660AD9D9" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"The Boss wants to talk to you," one of them growled, voice dripping with intimidation.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="495455C3" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito didn’t flinch. His smile remained steady, almost disarming. "Of course," he replied smoothly. "I’ll go see him right away." His calmness was unshaken, his gaze steady, as if the walls of muscle meant nothing at all.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="436B0450" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>They marched him down the corridor, flanking him on all sides, their footsteps heavy and stubborn. Upon reaching the office, they all but shoved him into the chair opposite Shimada-san's desk, the leather creaking under his weight. One of the enforcers entered into Hideyoshi’s office.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7B914F2B" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito maintained his composure, smoothing the front of his jacket with the casual grace of someone entirely unbothered by the rough handling. His expression remained pristine, untouched by the forceful escort.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="10972A39" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He sat calmly, hands clasped neatly in his lap, posture impeccable. Harsh afternoon light slashed through the blinds, carving jagged stripes across the carpet like bars of a gilded cage.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="123B7B17" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>A sharp buzz broke the silence, the signal unmistakable—Kurosawa was ready.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0EEDE58B" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa's face was flushed, eyes blazing with raw frustration. "That lying bitch!" he snarled, pacing behind his desk like a caged animal, each step heavy with barely contained rage. "You’re telling me she KNEW ALL ALONG AND DIDN’T TELL ME?!"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="578BC436" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito had just finished explaining the carefully constructed white lie, watching the furious storm unfold before him with measured calmness. His hands remained folded neatly in his lap, expression unreadable, while Kurosawa’s fury crashed against the walls like waves against rock.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="27F326BB" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"She knows nothing more. I made sure of it," Saito replied smoothly. "All she understands is that Miku-san needed rest, and she was too weak to refuse her."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3621A8FA" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="445C5EE1" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>Kurosawa halted mid-pace, his gaze snapping to Saito's with unbridled suspicion. "And you believe her? That snake lied to me twice already!"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="26B0B256" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito inclined his head, his expression serene. "She’s afraid," he conceded, his voice calm and measured. "But she’s not stupid. I can assure you she won’t lie again. If you’d like, you can speak to her yourself. I imagine she’s still too shaken to hide anything. She was nearly in tears when I spoke to her."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="63B6437D" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“And why in all hells were you at her flat giving her breakfast?! Why did she call you, of all people?! Doesn’t she have friends?!” Kurosawa spat, his pacing more erratic, fists clenched at his sides. “The other useless ‘idols’…”—he made quotation marks with his fingers, dripping with contempt—"…in this fucking agency. Why didn’t she call me?! I spent two goddamn years making that fucking bitch trust me. She even let me f—"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6247FFBB" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He cut himself off, jaw snapping shut, nostrils flaring with the effort to rein himself in. His eyes burned with rage, flickering dangerously before landing back on Saito. “Why you?!”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7F2A834B" w14:textId="7B85B0A9" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito remained unflinching, his expression calm and resolute. "Because," he replied evenly, his voice smooth, "she trusts me, Kurosawa-san. Ask anyone—she sees me like a father. I’ve been kind to her. And I was off that day. She was afraid of upsetting you, of how you might react." He paused, letting the weight of his words settle. "I mean, look at yourself—you can barely keep it together, sir. Can you blame her?"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1CFBD6B3" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>His tone was calm, almost clinical, each word calculated to land just right. "It’s as simple as that."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="04684DA6" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"And you know nothing…" Kurosawa pressed, his eyes narrowing to vicious slits. "She didn’t tell you a word?"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="30778AC2" w14:textId="4ECE3647" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"Not a word, Kurosawa-san," Saito replied smoothly. "I made her breakfast, brewed her te</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="0045160E">
              <w:t>a… she said it was menstrual cramps</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="002A1E3C">
              <w:t>. I made sure she was alright and</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="008436FE">
              <w:t>left</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>. As I mentioned, I had errands to run. We are busy men."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="751309D1" w14:textId="28FAC2C1" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">His tone dipped slightly on the last phrase, the weight on </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="002A1E3C">
              <w:t>‘we’</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> deliberate, coaxing Kurosawa to recognise him as an equal—someone with power, someone with understanding.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="766C92DB" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa's eyes narrowed further, suspicion simmering just beneath the surface. Yet, despite the lingering doubt, the explanation seemed to satiate his fury— at least for the moment. His breathing steadied, though his fists remained clenched, knuckles white with restrained rage. "Then who the fuck helped her escape?!"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3E4AC62F" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="55A1BED5" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">Saito paused, his gaze drifting for a moment as if combing through possibilities. When he looked back at Kurosawa, his eyes were steady and deliberate. "I believe we should </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>shift our focus," he said calmly. "We need to find Miku-san, not a scapegoat. Chasing after Nakayama-san or anyone else in this agency is a dead end. No one knows anything. I believe Miku-san acted alone."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3922CF57" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa's fist crashed down onto the desk, the impact rattling the surface and sending a tremor through the room. "Then where is she, Saito?! Tell me! Where do we even begin?" – The echoes of trust were already threading through the monster's mind, fragile yet growing, curling like smoke in the stagnant air. Saito watched the shift, subtle but unmistakable— the slightest softening in Kurosawa's gaze, the faintest edge of desperation lurking behind the fury.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="07790DE8" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito tilted his head slightly, his voice dropping to a near whisper. "Where was she from? Sapporo, wasn’t it? People go back to what they know… when they need comfort. Familiarity." His words hung in the air, deliberate and weighted. He paused, letting the suggestion settle, watching as Kurosawa’s expression shifted—eyes narrowing with sudden clarity, the idea taking root just as intended.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4A1733D4" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>It was a false lead, a trail carefully laid out for him to follow—away from his prey. Saito needed him to latch onto it, to be consumed by it. His gaze remained steady, calm, as if nothing more than a simple observation had slipped from his lips. But beneath the surface, he was setting the stage, pulling the strings.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="772C2ED8" w14:textId="3D80A81C" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">"If I may suggest," Saito continued, his tone smooth and measured, "instead of scattering our resources to find a culprit, we focus on Miku-san directly. If she returned </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00622F6E">
              <w:t>home</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>, we could find her. It would be cleaner… quieter. Less… exposure."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="750E04B5" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa stared at him, the gears visibly turning behind his eyes, grinding with purpose. Saito stepped forward, just enough to draw his focus entirely. "I’ll reach out to our contacts in Hokkaido," he said smoothly. "A simple check— nothing dramatic. If she’s there, we’ll know. If not, I’ll expand the search. Quietly."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="35D797DA" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa’s jaw tightened, muscles flexing beneath his skin, then gradually eased, the tension in his shoulders loosening—if only slightly. "Fine," he spat, though the venom had dulled. "Find her."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="2AE96907" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He had taken the bait.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="576EFB6C" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"And Takeguchi…" he added, voice low and deliberate.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="57B03BD2" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"Yes, Kurosawa-san?"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1EF3BC1C" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa’s eyes sharpened, glinting with something cold and predatory. "If she thinks she can run from me… she’s sorely mistaken."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="07844954" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="78FDD61B" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>Saito bowed deeply, the image of deference perfected. "Of course, sir. I’ll see to it personally." His tone was steady, unwavering, designed to reinforce the illusion—an accomplice, an equal. Someone Kurosawa could rely on. Someone dependable. This was the moment. That simple response was calculated to root the idea firmly in Kurosawa's mind. Trust. Loyalty. Control. The seed had been planted, and now it only needed time to take root.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3D0BCBA9" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>"I’ll have the first reports on your desk by tomorrow morning," Saito added, bowing slightly—not too deep, just enough to convey respect without submission. His posture remained firm, controlled, a gesture of professionalism rather than deference.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0890E3FF" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa gave a curt nod and turned back to the window, hands clasped behind his back. He stared out over the sprawling cityscape, the weight of power and fury draping his shoulders like a mantle, his reflection barely visible against the glass, overshadowed by the empire he ruled.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="398759B2" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito stepped out of the office, the door clicking shut with a soft finality. He adjusted his collar, straightened his sleeves, and strode down the corridor with the same measured grace he always carried. His mind was already moving—calculating, weaving whispers into false trails, buying Miku time with every delicate lie.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1888D403" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa's secretary and the brutes stationed nearby stared at him, eyes wide with disbelief. It was as if a ghost had walked past them—an old, unassuming man emerging from the beast's lair completely unharmed.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="543A4278" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>In his pocket, his phone vibrated—a single message. He didn’t check it. Not yet. First, he had a call to make. Hokkaido.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="5A14C517" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>It wouldn’t lead anywhere, of course. But it would lead just far enough away, for just long enough.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="69D9F8D7" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa leaned back in his chair, swirling the whisky in his glass with slow, deliberate movements. The amber liquid caught the fractured light, casting shards of gold across the polished surface of his desk. His fingers moved deftly over his mobile, dialling a number from memory—a number not saved in his contacts.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6A2C491D" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>The line clicked, connecting instantly. He didn’t bother with greetings. "There’s going to be a re-shifting," he said, his voice razor-sharp and devoid of warmth. "Megumi is finished. I want her gone by morning. Termination letter on her desk before she even steps foot inside."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="05733867" w14:textId="611FD780" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">He paused, swirling the whisky again, watching the ripples spread out from the centre—controlled, deliberate. "Takeguchi is going to be my eyes and ears now," he continued, his tone smooth and surgical. "Miku’s </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="0035762A">
              <w:t>gone, she escaped. She got herself knocked up and wants to hide it from us.</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="0035762A">
              <w:t>T</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>he press will be circling like vultures. I want control. Absolute control.</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00402C9E">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C10E99" w:rsidRPr="00C10E99">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">We need to keep her disappearance under wraps for as long as we </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C10E99" w:rsidRPr="00C10E99">
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>can—at least until we find her, or she misses so many events that we can’t cover it up anymore. And even then, no one can know she’s with child. I want Takeguchi to clamp down on the girls</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="004056AF">
              <w:t>, the press, everything</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C10E99" w:rsidRPr="00C10E99">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">. </w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="304771AE" w14:textId="2319FACF" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">He took a long, unhurried sip of whisky, savouring the burn. "Send Saito </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="002F7EDA">
              <w:t>Megumi’s</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> itinerary, her notes… everything. I want him fully integrated by morning. He’s taking her place. If he fails, he’s next."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3FE0E4C5" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa leaned back, his eyes narrowing to sharp slits. "And Nakayama…" he added, voice dropping to a glacial whisper. "She knows too much. I want her silenced."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="31B53B20" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>A pause. Muffled words on the other end— hesitation.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="10AA0123" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa's jaw clenched, the tendons straining beneath his skin, his grip on the glass so tight it seemed ready to shatter. "No, you idiot!" he snarled, his voice slicing through the line with venomous precision. "I’m not wasting money on forensics right now. We have an idol missing. I’m not paying to sweep up that kind of mess. Use your goddamn brain cells for once, will you?!"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="64FA4C44" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He paused, drawing in a slow, deliberate breath, his posture straightening as he calmed himself. When he spoke again, his voice was cold and measured, dripping with calculated malice. "Hand her a stack of cash and a one-way ticket to nowhere. Samoa, Tuvalu, Vanuatu—I don’t give a damn where. Make sure she understands she’s not coming back and that she’s trading silence for her life."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="714CC183" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Another pause, more murmuring. His eyes flared with contempt. "If she’s stupid enough to refuse, then we do it the hard way. And when I say hard, I mean she’s never found. Am I clear?"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="28A8C59D" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He listened for a moment, his expression unmoving. "Good. And make it clean. I want this mess erased by morning."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6DB1D7CC" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kurosawa took another sip of whisky, leaning back with the smug satisfaction of a king observing his pawns on a chessboard. "And one more thing," he added, voice dripping with ice. "If I find out anyone so much as whispers about this… you’re next."</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="5AB09D0D" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He ended the call with a tap of his finger, setting the glass down with a deliberate click. His reflection stared back at him from the polished surface, eyes sharp and unyielding. For Kurosawa, pawns existed to be moved—or removed.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4CD3F5F1" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito finished his shift with the same deliberate grace he always carried, his footsteps measured and silent against the polished floors. The building had long since emptied of its usual noise—the chatter of interns, the clipped heels of executives, the hushed whispers of idols passing through. Now, only the hum of the fluorescent lights and the distant murmur of the janitorial staff remained.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7A8F0E57" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>He straightened his desk, adjusted the pens to perfect alignment, and shut down his computer, watching the screen fade to black with a soft, satisfying click. He picked up his coat, draping it neatly over his arm, and reached for his mobile. As he did, the screen illuminated with a soft glow—a string of notifications cascading one after the other.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="5D26201B" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>From: sysadmin@yamakamusic.jp</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1AAA996E" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>To: takeguchi.s@yamakamusic.jp</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1DCCE0D6" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Subject: Access granted to Administration Sheet</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="57DA3D58" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>You have been granted access to Yamaka Music's Administration Sheet. Please use your security credentials to log in.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6A703D5F" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He raised an eyebrow, thumb sliding to the next notification.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6EEF4EA2" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>From: sysadmin@yamakamusic.jp</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6DA896FB" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>To: takeguchi.s@yamakamusic.jp</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="77B51E61" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Subject: Access granted to Idol Schedules</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7A5B7189" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>You now have full permissions to view, adjust, and manage the schedules of all active idols.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="211F902E" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Another one followed, then another.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="52EAEE7B" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>From: sysadmin@yamakamusic.jp</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="19CBC040" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>To: takeguchi.s@yamakamusic.jp</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="389B0961" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Subject: Access granted to Bookings</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="2EC39592" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>You have been granted administrative rights to manage and adjust all booking arrangements for Yamaka Music.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="204DD8E2" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>His eyes flicked over each new message as they continued to pour in.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="65861D95" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>From: sysadmin@yamakamusic.jp</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6529C1E8" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>To: takeguchi.s@yamakamusic.jp</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0E00C6E3" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Subject: Access granted to Personnel Files</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4EDAB1A1" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>You now have full administrative access to personnel records for all active and archived employees.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="36DD4C0C" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="62BB4B0A" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>From: sysadmin@yamakamusic.jp</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="463AA0F0" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>To: takeguchi.s@yamakamusic.jp</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="523CFD04" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>Subject: Access granted to Event Management System</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="08C35687" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>You now have permissions to view, schedule, and manage all upcoming events and public appearances.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="48DB24E0" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="1A22892F" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>From: sysadmin@yamakamusic.jp</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="39F58174" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>To: takeguchi.s@yamakamusic.jp</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1A740D85" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Subject: Access granted to Crisis Response Protocols</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="71375AA4" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>You are now authorised to review and execute crisis management protocols as needed. Your access is active immediately.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="739D2FAC" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="703AE17A" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>It went on and on, email after email, cascading like digital rain, each one extending his reach deeper and deeper into the heart of Yamaka Music. A slow smile crept onto his face, hidden behind the smooth veneer of professionalism.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1DE8F93D" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He slipped the phone back into his pocket, smoothing the front of his jacket as he stepped into the empty corridor. The soft click of his shoes echoed in the silence, measured and composed. His fingers tapped idly against his thigh, the rhythm matching his steps.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0DAE4CA4" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>As he reached the lift, he pressed the button and waited, gaze fixed on the digital numbers descending. The doors slid open with a quiet whisper, and he stepped inside. He adjusted his collar, straightened his sleeves, and glanced once more at his reflection. Calm. Polished. Untouchable.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="72BEDAE2" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>When the doors slid shut, Saito's smile returned, sharper this time, flickering just at the edges of his mouth. He closed his eyes for just a moment, savouring the feeling. Bingo.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1EE00FDB" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He was in. After years of patience and precision, of working two lives—one in the underbelly of Yamaka Music, the other within the PSIA— he was finally inside the circle. The walls he had spent years chipping away at had finally cracked.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="14CD12DD" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He straightened his back, feeling the weight of the keys now in his possession. Years of preparation, of undercover double shifts, of accounts under false names, and falsified reports had finally paid off. All the detours, all the close calls, every moment he had bitten his tongue and bowed his head—it all led to this.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1A5954A5" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito opened his eyes as the elevator descended, the floor numbers lighting up one by one. He inhaled deeply, letting the sensation of power fill his lungs. Slowly, methodically, he would tear it all down.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3A8706C2" w14:textId="36039B4C" w:rsidR="00B73C2D" w:rsidRDefault="00E237B0" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Sakura Dream, the idols, the entire empire. From the inside.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3647E570" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="007C710C" w:rsidRDefault="007C710C" w:rsidP="00E237B0" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="64C5328E" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00C5653B" w:rsidRDefault="007C710C" w:rsidP="007C710C">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">The door clicked shut with a gentle whisper, and Saito stood alone in his </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C5653B">
              <w:t>flat.</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C5653B">
              <w:t>T</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>he silence folding around him like a heavy cloak.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="01B3594D" w14:textId="6BC7A300" w:rsidR="007C710C" w:rsidRDefault="007C710C" w:rsidP="007C710C">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He slipped off his shoes, the familiar scuff of leather against the entryway tile grounding him, though his mind drifted far from Tokyo. He moved with deliberate ease, fingers brushing across the polished wood of the cabinet before him, eyes lingering for just a moment on the thin film of dust collected on its surface.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="32DBE7CE" w14:textId="7C315FA7" w:rsidR="007C710C" w:rsidRDefault="007C710C" w:rsidP="007C710C">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He hesitated, then reached for the drawer. His hand closed around the cold metal of the old rotary phone, untouched for years but still maintained—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C5653B">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>out of habit, perhaps, or something more deeply embedded. His fingers dialled the number with the fluidity of muscle memory, each digit falling into place without thought. A number committed to heart long ago, before Tokyo, before the PSIA, before everything.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="163050AE" w14:textId="4BD03820" w:rsidR="007C710C" w:rsidRDefault="007C710C" w:rsidP="007C710C">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">The line clicked, static whispering faintly, stretching long and </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C5653B">
              <w:t>unbending</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">. For a moment, he wondered if it was still connected at all. But then, the shrill, unmistakable ring echoed across the line, travelling miles, cutting through </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C5653B">
              <w:t>space</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> and time.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="03C4CB67" w14:textId="0E060F13" w:rsidR="007C710C" w:rsidRDefault="007C710C" w:rsidP="007C710C">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>It rang out into the quiet of the Butterfly Heaven Shrine, its sound disrupting the stillness with the soft clatter of old machinery. Papers shuffled in the office, disturbed by the vibration—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C5653B">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>the prayer requests, the notes, the schedules all shifting ever so slightly, as if the phone’s ring itself had shaken loose the dust of forgotten years.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="5551A5D0" w14:textId="52EE9347" w:rsidR="007C710C" w:rsidRDefault="007C710C" w:rsidP="007C710C">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Outside, the scent of cedar and incense drifted on the wind. Takahashi Kōji knelt before the altar, lighting incense with a practised hand, the thin tendrils of smoke curling upwards, spiralling into the air like whispered prayers. His movements were steady, deliberate, hands clasped in reverence before the shrine</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C5653B">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> to the Kami of Rebirth.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="615C23BE" w14:textId="2594EE73" w:rsidR="007C710C" w:rsidRDefault="007C710C" w:rsidP="007C710C">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>The phone rang again, sharper this time, insistently cutting through the soft crackle of burning incense. Kōji’s eyes flickered open, his hands pausing in mid-gesture. He straightened slowly, the joints of his knees protesting softly as he rose. He turned, gaze settling on the small, dust-covered receiver perched on the corner of the office, its cord twisted and brittle from years of disuse.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="34763C50" w14:textId="1E474D54" w:rsidR="007C710C" w:rsidRDefault="007C710C" w:rsidP="007C710C">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">He did not move </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C5653B">
              <w:t>immediately;</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> his eyes locked on the device as if it were some relic of a distant past that had no business intruding on the present. No one called that phone anymore. He wasn’t even sure it worked. Anyone who needed him knew his mobile. Yet there it was, ringing stubbornly, demanding attention.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1D8E5D47" w14:textId="36F4A081" w:rsidR="007C710C" w:rsidRDefault="007C710C" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kōji stepped forward, each footfall measured, deliberate. His fingers wrapped around the receiver, lifting it to his ear, the sound of distant static crackling softly. He said nothing, waiting, the silence stretching between them, heavy and unspoken.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="470820DE" w14:textId="306E5A5F" w:rsidR="00DD38B1" w:rsidRDefault="00DD38B1" w:rsidP="00DD38B1">
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>The line held, unbroken, until a breath whispered through, distant and unmistakably familiar.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7A245E42" w14:textId="148DB399" w:rsidR="00DD38B1" w:rsidRDefault="00DD38B1" w:rsidP="00DD38B1">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“Kōji…”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="386D0CB0" w14:textId="1B2FBA31" w:rsidR="00DD38B1" w:rsidRDefault="00DD38B1" w:rsidP="00DD38B1">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>The word lingered in the space between them, suspended on the edge of memory and distance.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0D832EAB" w14:textId="01C2CE54" w:rsidR="00DD38B1" w:rsidRDefault="00DD38B1" w:rsidP="00DD38B1">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kōji closed his eyes, the breath of incense heavy around him, and for the first time in many years, he spoke into the old receiver, voice soft and steady.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6F992147" w14:textId="297226F6" w:rsidR="00DD38B1" w:rsidRDefault="00DD38B1" w:rsidP="00DD38B1">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“Saito.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="70D756DB" w14:textId="36C728BE" w:rsidR="00DD38B1" w:rsidRDefault="00DD38B1" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>And then silence—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C5653B">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">thick and </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C5653B">
              <w:t>obstinate</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">, stretching out like a bridge between </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C5653B">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">the peace of </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kamiyama Cove and the chaos of Tokyo.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="24664F18" w14:textId="378002F0" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="006F5000" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>The line stretched thin, a tether between distant lives and distant years. Kōji leaned against the wooden frame of the shrine’s office. His fingers held the receiver with a sense of disbelief—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C5653B">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>he hadn’t heard this voice in decades, yet the familiarity settled in like dust on old wood.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6E69B3B9" w14:textId="44FD8BED" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="006F5000" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“It has been… what? Twenty years?” Kōji’s voice slipped through the receiver, gentle but clear, a ripple on still water.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="49042A9A" w14:textId="18BBF15D" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="006F5000" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">“Twenty-five… this June.” Saito’s reply came steady and </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00C5653B">
              <w:t>obdurate;</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> the weight of those years held between syllables.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="09C6E288" w14:textId="7D274DC7" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="006F5000" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kōji’s gaze drifted to the window, where sunlight spilled through the paper screens, casting pale patterns across the floor. “To what do I owe the honour?” There was warmth in his tone, tempered by the strangeness of it all.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7F4C0459" w14:textId="67DFD90E" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="006F5000" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito hesitated, silence stretching like a held breath. “I need a favour…”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="68FD283E" w14:textId="34BCC2CE" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="00910F77" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00910F77">
              <w:t>Kōji waited with the patience of a man whose time is not measured in seconds, but in seasons; phone cradled against his ear, the air thick with anticipation. Outside, the wind stirred the branches of the old Keyaki— a type of Elm Tree, whose leaves drifted to the ground like whispers in the twilight.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7F4E8398" w14:textId="6F8C3A28" w:rsidR="002E4E9D" w:rsidRDefault="002E4E9D" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002E4E9D">
              <w:t>“A girl arrived at Kamiyama Cove this morning,” Saito continued, his tone deliberate and measured. “Her name is Mori Misaki.” He paused, the name hanging in the air. “She’s…” Another pause, the weight of it stretching across the line. His breath faltered, as if the very memory of it were sharp. “She’s been touched by darkness… scarred by the cruelty of someone she once trusted. There are wounds that cannot be seen, shadows that linger long after they are cast.” His voice softened, almost reverent. “I’ve sent her to Butterfly Heaven. The place is hers now</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="001B0E51">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">. </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002E4E9D">
              <w:t>You and I both know… that house’s blessings allow people to start again. The Butterfly Kami watches over it still… her presence lingers in the walls, healing what is broken.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="2C89321A" w14:textId="0C705D42" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="001B0E51" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="001B0E51">
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>Kōji watched the incense smoke curl upwards, spiralling gently, as if dancing to the rhythm of the wind. His gaze softened. “A wise choice,” he replied, his voice gentle and contemplative. “The Butterfly Kami’s blessing lingers there still… her wings brushing the walls like whispers. That place has always been touched by her grace.” He paused, the unspoken question lingering between them. “But why do you need me?”</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="786C3241" w14:textId="3A27CEBF" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="001B0E51" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="001B0E51">
              <w:t>“She needs someone she can trust,</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00124C5D">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> a</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="001B0E51">
              <w:t>nd I need someone I can trust to watch over her… someone who understands the spirits of that place. The Butterfly Kami watches, but her hands can only reach those who have understood her power. Misaki will need guidance.” He paused, his breath softening. “I trust no one else more.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3E17E30B" w14:textId="5539E834" w:rsidR="001B0E51" w:rsidRDefault="001B0E51" w:rsidP="001B0E51">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>There was a silence, the kind that spoke of old bonds and unspoken understanding. Kōji exhaled. “I see,” he said finally. “I’ll—”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="63F581BD" w14:textId="1DB8EDBB" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="001B0E51" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“Kōji,” Saito’s voice cut through the line, sharp and edged with a plea that almost caught in his breath. “You can’t ask her about her life before Kamiyama Cove. You can’t ask her who she is, nor why she’s there… The past is hers alone, buried where it belongs. If it must be spoken, it will be by her hand, not yours.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="15EBE801" w14:textId="7546F811" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="006F5000" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kōji absorbed the request with a stillness that came from years of devotion and patience. His eyes drifted to the smoke spiralling from the incense, curling towards the rafters and disappearing into shadows. “If that’s what you need,” he replied</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00741168">
              <w:t>.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="50949B02" w14:textId="0AD40201" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="006F5000" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“It is…” Saito</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00741168">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> said finally</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>,</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00741168">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> his voice</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> edged with something unspoken. “Please deliver her a note. Tell her to check the old mailbox by the steps of the shrine…” He paused, and Kōji could almost hear the ghost of a smile in his words. “Remember the war games we used to play?”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="03E35F41" w14:textId="025DA0E1" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="006F5000" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>A slow smile crept onto Kōji’s face, gentle and warm. “I do,” he chuckled, the sound brushing away years in an instant. “Dearly.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1443D568" w14:textId="2994B116" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="006F5000" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">Outside the shrine, the wind stirred, brushing through the bamboo with a whisper of distant laughter. Their childhood had been painted with shadows and secrets—messages hidden in the shrine’s </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00124C5D">
              <w:t>announcements;</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> holes punched in cardboard to align with the right words. They had been spies, or at least they pretended to be.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="12B31540" w14:textId="485A5CBA" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="006F5000" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kōji chuckled again, glancing back at the dust-covered receiver. “It seems,” he said, his voice almost wistful, “we’re playing spies again.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="53BB74D3" w14:textId="4DA42D34" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="006F5000" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“Seems so,” Saito replied, the nostalgia settling like dust on old memories.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="597DA4BB" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="006F5000" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kōji straightened, glancing out the window as the wind brushed past the paper screens, carrying the scent of rain from the mountains. “I’ll watch over her,” he murmured, his voice firm and resolute. “Mori Misaki is safe in Kamiyama Cove. You have my word.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="44259138" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="006F5000" w:rsidP="006F5000" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="7040F1C6" w14:textId="6A7C4A37" w:rsidR="006F5000" w:rsidRDefault="006F5000" w:rsidP="006F5000">
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>There was a pause, and then a click. The line went dead, and the silence returned—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00124C5D">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">settling back into the corners of the shrine, curling around the incense smoke like it had always belonged. Kōji set the receiver back into its cradle with deliberate care. Outside, the wind stirred the branches of the </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:t>Keyaki</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> tree once more, scattering </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:t>leaves</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> like whispered promises.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="238B1238" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRDefault="00E058E8" w:rsidP="00E237B0" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="72251B9C" w14:textId="7FDBB9AA" w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRDefault="00E058E8" w:rsidP="00E058E8">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">The sun hung low over Kamiyama Cove, casting long shadows that stretched across the wooden floor of the shrine’s office. Dust motes drifted lazily in the fading light as Takahashi Kōji moved with calm precision, his hands steady and assured. He reached for </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">last week’s </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>shrine announcements, the thick parchment crisp beneath his fingertips.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="065A7A44" w14:textId="026F5457" w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRDefault="00E058E8" w:rsidP="00E058E8">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">He scanned the lines of </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:t>characters</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>, eyes flickering over each character with a practised gaze. He knew what he was searching for—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">the right symbols, the perfect alignment. Once he found them, he pulled a heavy sheet of </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">white </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003E5CAD">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>washi</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> paper from the drawer, its surface smooth. With deliberate care, he marked the locations of each character onto the </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:t>paper</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>, adding a numbered order beside each marking, inscribing the traditional numerals elegantly alongside each stroke.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="2F778D60" w14:textId="4FF6A88F" w:rsidR="003A63D5" w:rsidRDefault="00E058E8" w:rsidP="00E058E8">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">Satisfied with the placements, Kōji punched small, precise holes through the markings. </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003E5CAD">
              <w:t>The</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> washi whispering under the pressure of the pen, yielding gracefully. When he finished, he placed the template over the shrine announcement, aligning it with a practised hand. His eyes lit up as the message emerged, clear a</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:t>s day.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="25168E61" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRDefault="00E058E8" w:rsidP="00E058E8" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="150B5E0D" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="003A63D5" w:rsidRDefault="003A63D5" w:rsidP="00C5653B">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:ind w:left="720" />
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>(</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>一</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">) </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>歓迎、</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>(</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>二</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">) </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>神</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>社</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>、</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> (</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>三</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">) </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>安</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>全</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>、</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> (</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>四</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">) </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>神</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>主</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>、</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> (</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>五</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">) </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>竹、</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> (</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>六</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">) </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>口、</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> (</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>七</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">) </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>友</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>達、</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>(</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>八</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">) </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>宜</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>し</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>く、</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>(</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>九</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">) </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>待</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>て</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>、</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>(</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>十</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">) </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" w:hint="eastAsia" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>手紙</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6BA4F328" w14:textId="2639DE21" w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRPr="00C5653B" w:rsidRDefault="00565143" w:rsidP="00C5653B">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:ind w:left="720" />
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>(</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>1</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>)W</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">elcome, </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>(</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>2</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>)S</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">hrine, </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>(</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>3</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>)S</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">afety, </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>(</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>4</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>)P</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">riest, </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>(</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>5</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>)T</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">ake, </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>(</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>6</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>)G</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">uchi, </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>(</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>7</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>)F</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">riend, </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>(</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>8</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>)P</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">lease, </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>(</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>9</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>)A</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">wait, </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> (1</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003A63D5">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>0</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>)M</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRPr="00C5653B">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>essage.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="32113D45" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRDefault="00E058E8" w:rsidP="00E058E8" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="6C0F5BD6" w14:textId="44AD4E24" w:rsidR="00E058E8" w:rsidRDefault="00E058E8" w:rsidP="00E058E8">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>A smile spread across his face, nostalgia seeping into his expression. It had been years since the game was played, and yet the simplicity of it still held a kind of magic. He folded the template neatly and set it aside with reverence, his fingers brushing its edge before letting go.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1F0F9E24" w14:textId="25601CC3" w:rsidR="00565143" w:rsidRDefault="00565143" w:rsidP="00565143">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">Reaching for a fresh sheet of </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003E5CAD">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>Shuinshi</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003E5CAD">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>a beautifully textured washi paper reserved for sacred inscriptions and blessings—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003E5CAD">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kōji held it up to the lantern light. Its surface was adorned with a delicate pre-stamped image</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003E5CAD">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> of</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> a butterfly mid-flight, wings outstretched in hues of soft pink and blue. Behind it, </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="003E5CAD">
              <w:t>Sakura</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> petals drifted in elegant spirals, captured in a moment of perpetual spring. The design was intricate and serene, a symbol of transformation and rebirth fitting for the note he was about to inscribe.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="35329B8D" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00565143" w:rsidRDefault="00565143" w:rsidP="00565143" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="484CD40D" w14:textId="0C9E41FD" w:rsidR="00565143" w:rsidRDefault="003E5CAD" w:rsidP="00565143">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003E5CAD">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">Kōji dipped his brush into the ink, its bristles soaking up the rich black liquid before he pressed it to the page. His strokes were deliberate, flowing with the elegance of years of practice, each one unfurling with the grace of ritual. He wrote with the same care and precision reserved for </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003E5CAD">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>Goshuin</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003E5CAD">
              <w:t>—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="003E5CAD">
              <w:t>those sacred stamps and inscriptions collected by pilgrims at shrines; each one a mark of devotion and memory pressed into paper. The ink spread across the Shuinshi smoothly, its fibres absorbing the calligraphy with reverence, preserving each stroke in perfect clarity.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="43C6F1F9" w14:textId="0BD76FF9" w:rsidR="00770FC0" w:rsidRDefault="00770FC0" w:rsidP="00565143">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>::tg::</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          
          <w:p w14:paraId="581BE3BC" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="001A3759" w:rsidRPr="001A3759" w:rsidRDefault="001A3759" w:rsidP="001A3759">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r>
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>蝶の楽園へようこそ。</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          
          <w:p w14:paraId="40FC7797" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="001A3759" w:rsidRPr="001A3759" w:rsidRDefault="001A3759" w:rsidP="001A3759">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r>
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>竹林の中、神社へ続く</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>石段の麓にある郵便箱</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>はあなたのものです。</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          
          <w:p w14:paraId="3084C2F5" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="001A3759" w:rsidRPr="001A3759" w:rsidRDefault="001A3759" w:rsidP="001A3759">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r>
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>添付された鍵を使っ</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>て開けてください。</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          
          <w:p w14:paraId="70380871" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="001A3759" w:rsidRPr="001A3759" w:rsidRDefault="001A3759" w:rsidP="001A3759">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r>
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>よろしくお願いします。</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          
          <w:p w14:paraId="30A8D648" w14:textId="552FFD47" w:rsidR="001A3759" w:rsidRPr="001A3759" w:rsidRDefault="001A3759" w:rsidP="001A3759">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r>
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>竹の森の入口の友より。</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00770FC0">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:br />
              <w:t>::/tg::</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="751A5CDF" w14:textId="090C8FF8" w:rsidR="00C5653B" w:rsidRPr="00F346BE" w:rsidRDefault="00C5653B" w:rsidP="00D77E08">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:spacing w:after="0" />
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F346BE">
              <w:t>Welcome to Butterfly Heaven.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0F69BE1E" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00C5653B" w:rsidRPr="00F346BE" w:rsidRDefault="00C5653B" w:rsidP="00D77E08">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:spacing w:after="0" />
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F346BE">
              <w:t>The mailbox at the feet of the stone stairs to the Shrine in the grove is yours.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6AB690AF" w14:textId="5CF50943" w:rsidR="00C5653B" w:rsidRPr="00F346BE" w:rsidRDefault="00C5653B" w:rsidP="00D77E08">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:spacing w:after="0" />
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F346BE">
              <w:t>Use the attached key to open it.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="78D973BF" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00C5653B" w:rsidRPr="00F346BE" w:rsidRDefault="00C5653B" w:rsidP="00D77E08">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:spacing w:after="0" />
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F346BE">
              <w:t>Kind regards,</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="03A8E0D1" w14:textId="493A4EFD" w:rsidR="00565143" w:rsidRPr="00F346BE" w:rsidRDefault="00C5653B" w:rsidP="00D77E08">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:spacing w:after="0" />
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F346BE">
              <w:t>A friend at the Entrance of the Bamboo Forest.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="780584AD" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00C5653B" w:rsidRDefault="00C5653B" w:rsidP="00C5653B" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="2D9C8B70" w14:textId="4127B75A" w:rsidR="00565143" w:rsidRDefault="00565143" w:rsidP="00565143">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kōji lifted the brush, allowing the ink to settle into the fibres of the paper, the scent of fresh ink mingling with the subtle traces of cedar that lingered in the room. He examined his work, nodding with quiet satisfaction before setting the brush aside.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="26CF13AE" w14:textId="1D91DE50" w:rsidR="00D77E08" w:rsidRDefault="00D77E08" w:rsidP="00D77E08">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>The Shuinshi, with its bold characters and delicate pre-stamped imagery, seemed to glow softly in the lantern light— a sacred promise folded into the fragility of paper. He waited for the ink to dry, the air heavy with the quiet stillness of the shrine, before folding the note with reverence and slipping it into a crisp envelope. Alongside it, he placed a small copper key— its handle shaped like butterfly wings, graceful and intricate, as if crafted to unlock not just a mailox, but possibilities.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="7132CDAE" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00D77E08" w:rsidRDefault="00D77E08" w:rsidP="00D77E08" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="72B8525E" w14:textId="2AD15956" w:rsidR="00565143" w:rsidRDefault="00D77E08" w:rsidP="00565143">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He sealed the envelope with a drop of crimson wax, pressing the shrine’s emblem into its surface— a butterfly encircled by kanji, the symbol of rebirth and sanctuary. The wax settled, cooling into permanence, as if binding the promise to the world itself.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="77089AF6" w14:textId="7744CA0D" w:rsidR="00D77E08" w:rsidRDefault="00565143" w:rsidP="00E058E8">
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>The envelope, now marked with the weight of tradition and promise, rested gently in his hands, heavier than mere paper should be. Kōji regarded it for a moment longer, his fingertips brushing the edges before he set it aside, ready for the next step.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="683D8931" w14:textId="3C5D0665" w:rsidR="008E6319" w:rsidRDefault="00E058E8" w:rsidP="00E237B0">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kōji set it aside, ready for delivery, and glanced out the window where the bamboo swayed gently in the breeze. Outside, the wind carried the scent of cedar and the whisper of old secrets. Kamiyama Cove, once again, would keep its promises.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="39B52982" w14:textId="29C4DED7" w:rsidR="008E6319" w:rsidRDefault="00A63347" w:rsidP="008E6319">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00A63347">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">He stood, brushing invisible dust from his robes, and made his way down the wooden steps of the shrine, the soft creak of the engawa stretching beneath his weight. The breeze whispered through the bamboo grove, carrying with it the scent of </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00E64EA3" w:rsidRPr="00910F77">
              <w:t>Keyaki</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00A63347">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> and a faint touch of salt from the distant sea. Ahead, the sun dipped lower, spreading a haze of amber across the stone path that descended the steps of the shrine, turning the scattered leaves to gold. His sandals struck the cobblestone with a gentle rhythm—steady, unhurried—the sound a familiar echo that had whispered through these grounds for as long as he could remember.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4AB8DE87" w14:textId="0D1160F7" w:rsidR="00A63347" w:rsidRDefault="00A63347" w:rsidP="00A63347">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>As he descended, the crimson Torii gate at the foot of the stone steps came into view, its silhouette stark against the fading light. Its shadow stretched long and solemn across the path, casting dark lines over the priest as he made his way down. He noted the flaking paint along its wooden beams, the vibrant red now dulled and chipped, whispering of seasons long passed.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="2662B6DB" w14:textId="73E58F36" w:rsidR="00A63347" w:rsidRDefault="00A63347" w:rsidP="00A63347">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kōji's gaze shifted to the old iron mailbox beside the gate— empty today, as it often was, though not always. Occasionally, it would cradle folded bills— electricity, telephone—the mundane tendrils of the modern world reaching up into this sacred place. But on most days, its iron belly remained hollow, untouched by paper or ink.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="677E54E4" w14:textId="24AFBB9A" w:rsidR="008E6319" w:rsidRDefault="00A63347" w:rsidP="00A63347">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>He approached it with quiet familiarity, sliding the punched template and the shrine announcements through the narrow slot. The soft rasp of paper against metal broke the stillness, a fleeting sound swallowed by the whisper of the wind. His fingertips lingered on the cold iron for a moment, absorbing its chill as if grounding himself in the present. Then, with a final glance, he pulled away and continued down the dirt and gravel path, his footsteps blending into the rhythm of the grove.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="75056421" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00A63347" w:rsidRDefault="00A63347" w:rsidP="00A63347">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>The trail snaked through the bamboo forest, shadows stretching long and thin as the canopy thickened above. Kōji moved with practised ease, ducking beneath low-hanging branches, his sandals pressing softly into the gravel with each step. The air grew heavier with the scent of salt and greenery, the distant breath of the sea threading through the grove.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6ADF42F7" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00A63347" w:rsidRDefault="00A63347" w:rsidP="00A63347" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="63B00D1F" w14:textId="4608FFAB" w:rsidR="00A63347" w:rsidRDefault="00A63347" w:rsidP="00A63347">
            <w:r>
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>Ahead, Butterfly Heaven emerged from the bamboo’s embrace, its silhouette softened by the gentle sway of the stalks. The house seemed cradled by the landscape, ancient and silent, as if it had always been there— an unyielding part of the earth itself.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="290F4DE6" w14:textId="73F449B5" w:rsidR="008E6319" w:rsidRDefault="00A63347" w:rsidP="00A63347">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Farther off, the sea shimmered faintly beyond the cliff at the far end of the garden, its surface catching the last glimmers of daylight. A bamboo fence stretched across its edge, weathered yet resolute, guarding the precipice with quiet dignity. The sun, now dipping low, cast its final rays with the softness of a farewell, retreating slowly behind the horizon as if slipping into slumber.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0C52B836" w14:textId="1647D198" w:rsidR="002123DC" w:rsidRDefault="002123DC" w:rsidP="002123DC">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Kōji released a soft breath, letting the image before him settle into his senses— the sea stretching endlessly beyond the cliff, its surface glimmering beneath the waning light. In the garden, the great cherry tree stood in solitary splendour, its branches reaching skyward as if searching for the distant elm that guarded the shrine. They were companions once, their tops swaying together under the moon's gaze, separated now by the winding stretch of bamboo that grew like a barrier of time. Two lovers whose paths had been severed by fate, forced to whisper to one another through the rustling leaves.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4CDB8FCC" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="002123DC" w:rsidRDefault="002123DC" w:rsidP="002123DC">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002123DC">
              <w:t>And there, nestled against the gentle sway of the grove, </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002123DC">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>Butterfly Heaven</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002123DC">
              <w:t> stood serene and untouched by time, its wooden beams and thatched roof unchanging, untouched even by the wear of the seasons. It rested in quiet defiance against the slow crawl of years, preserved in stillness, as if time itself had passed it by.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="16BBFC24" w14:textId="0B5EDCDF" w:rsidR="002123DC" w:rsidRDefault="002123DC" w:rsidP="002123DC">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Memories washed over him, unbidden but welcome. Endless summer afternoons with Saito, the two of them tearing through the grove with bamboo stalks fashioned into makeshift swords, their laughter tumbling through the canopy. For a moment, the years seemed to fold back, the weight of time lifting, replaced by the lightness of youth. The scent of grass, the sting of scraped knees, the echo of Saito's voice calling out his name... it lingered, like a ghost that refused to fade.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="44C4B497" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="002123DC" w:rsidRDefault="002123DC" w:rsidP="002123DC">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>And then, the spell broke.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="780A5197" w14:textId="7F86D680" w:rsidR="008E6319" w:rsidRDefault="00A63347" w:rsidP="00A63347">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>That was when he saw her.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="44415C13" w14:textId="0C9A8FDC" w:rsidR="002123DC" w:rsidRPr="002123DC" w:rsidRDefault="002123DC" w:rsidP="002123DC">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002123DC">
              <w:t>A flash of movement caught his eye—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002123DC">
              <w:t>slender and quick, almost surreal. A girl, darting across the garden, her skin pale like porcelain, hair trailing behind her in waves of brilliant teal that shimmered even in the twilight. Kōji flinched, breath catching in his throat. It was an eerie image against the tranquil landscape; the sheer vibrancy of her hair seemed to defy the muted hues of the setting sun, as if she carried her own light. Ghostly strands spilled over her shoulders like liquid jade, shifting and swaying with each step.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0EE11AC9" w14:textId="10860861" w:rsidR="008E6319" w:rsidRDefault="002123DC" w:rsidP="008E6319">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002123DC">
              <w:t>Her figure was delicate yet striking, the kind of beauty that seemed at odds with her fragility—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002123DC">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">slim arms, graceful limbs, and an elegance that bordered on ethereal. For a </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002123DC">
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>moment, she seemed less like a girl and more like a spirit</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2F58">
              <w:t>, a</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>yōkai</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2F58">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2F58" w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58">
              <w:t>or an</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2F58">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2F58" w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>onryō</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002123DC">
              <w:t>, flitting through the garden as if bound to it, as if she had always been there, waiting to be seen.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="297AC480" w14:textId="53F399A0" w:rsidR="00FD2F58" w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58" w:rsidRDefault="00FD2F58" w:rsidP="00FD2F58">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58">
              <w:t>But then he saw the details. She was running, clutching her stomach, her figure dressed in nothing but a brassiere too large for her frame and underpants that clung awkwardly to her hips—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">clothing that betrayed her </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>ethereal image and gave away her humanity</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">. No spirit would wear Victoria's Secret. Her bare feet skimmed over the soft moss and dirt, delicate and swift, as if sandals or proper footwear were mere afterthoughts in her </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>hurry to wherever she was heading</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58">
              <w:t>.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="18F7B741" w14:textId="43598057" w:rsidR="008E6319" w:rsidRDefault="00FD2F58" w:rsidP="008E6319">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58">
              <w:t>For a moment, he simply stared, frozen by the surreal quality of it—the oneiric strangeness that blurred the line between dream and waking. Her teal hair spilled behind her like threads of jade, shimmering even in the fading light, trailing her movements like whispers of another world.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="723DE5A4" w14:textId="3B66AFB6" w:rsidR="008E6319" w:rsidRDefault="008E6319" w:rsidP="008E6319">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">His eyes narrowed with </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2F58">
              <w:t>the voice of Saito on the back of his head</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">. </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2F58">
              <w:t>“</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>Do not ask questions</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2F58">
              <w:t>”</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">. </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2F58">
              <w:t>The</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> words rang clear in his mind, echoing through the silence. Kōji swallowed hard, averting his gaze as she disappeared around the corner of the annex, the wooden door of the outdoor toilet creaking open before slamming shut with finality. </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2F58">
              <w:t>“Oh” he let go softly to himself. “So it was that, she’s human after all” he giggled and then</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> let out a breath he hadn’t realised he was holding, shoulders sagging with the release.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3096B282" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00FD2F58" w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58" w:rsidRDefault="00FD2F58" w:rsidP="00FD2F58">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58">
              <w:t>His eyes narrowed, Saito's voice whispering at the back of his mind. </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>“Do not ask questions.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58">
              <w:t> The words rang clear, echoing through the silence with a weight that settled heavy in his chest. Kōji swallowed hard, instinctively averting his gaze as she disappeared around the corner of the annex. The wooden door of the outdoor toilet creaked open, then slammed shut with a startling finality.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="204AF554" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00FD2F58" w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58" w:rsidRDefault="00FD2F58" w:rsidP="00FD2F58">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58">
              <w:t>“Oh...” he breathed out softly, the sound barely a whisper. “So that was it... she’s human after all.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1657F059" w14:textId="2F0103CC" w:rsidR="008E6319" w:rsidRDefault="00FD2F58" w:rsidP="008E6319">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2F58">
              <w:t>A chuckle escaped him, unbidden and light, breaking the tension he hadn’t realised had wound him so tight. He let out a breath he’d been holding, shoulders sagging with the release, his hand finding its way to the back of his neck. For a moment, the absurdity of it washed over him, and he chuckled again, softer this time, as if sharing a secret with the wind.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="72562AA0" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E64EA3" w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3" w:rsidRDefault="00E64EA3" w:rsidP="00E64EA3">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>He stepped forward, moving through the gravel path that led to the main road. The old gate groaned as he pulled it open, its rusted metal scraping against itself in a long, aching chirr that shattered the silence of the grove. The sound sent crows fluttering from their perches, black wings cutting through the twilight as they scattered into the canopy above, their cries lingering in the stillness.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6EAE37D4" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E64EA3" w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3" w:rsidRDefault="00E64EA3" w:rsidP="00E64EA3">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>Kōji continued along the pebbled path that wove through the garden, each step a soft whisper against the stones. He reached the main entrance, stepping up onto the wooden boards of the </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>engawa</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>, their surface worn smooth by years of quiet footsteps. He slid the </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>shōji</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t> door open just enough for his hand and the envelope to slip through, the paper-thin door gliding with a hushed whisper.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="59D3591E" w14:textId="3A292768" w:rsidR="008E6319" w:rsidRDefault="00E64EA3" w:rsidP="008E6319">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>He placed the envelope carefully on the small side table near the entrance—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>a place meant for keys and letters, a silent witness to comings and goings. The copper key lay heavy within the envelope. Beside it, the letter, written in flowing calligraphy, rested neatly—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>an unspoken promise folded into crisp paper, waiting for hands that would soon come to claim it.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="21976FF1" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E64EA3" w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3" w:rsidRDefault="00E64EA3" w:rsidP="00E64EA3">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>Kōji stepped back, his hands coming together in a soft clap—a gesture of respect to the house and its spirits, a wordless acknowledgment of presence. The sound echoed faintly, slipping into the walls of Butterfly Heaven like a whispered blessing. With deliberate care, he slid the shōji door shut, the motion delicate and reverent, as if sealing a promise. The wooden frame settled into place with the gentleness of a final breath, the sound barely a whisper in the stillness that lingered in the air.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="49AE35DC" w14:textId="72604F81" w:rsidR="00E64EA3" w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3" w:rsidRDefault="00E64EA3" w:rsidP="00E64EA3">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">Without </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>a</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> word, Kōji turned and retraced his steps through the grove, the path folding him back into the shadows. The bamboo stirred softly in his wake, whispering enigmas only the wind could carry. The sun sank deeper into the horizon, casting long fingers of light that stretched through the stalks before fading into dusk.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3B551370" w14:textId="22B2BB1B" w:rsidR="00E64EA3" w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3" w:rsidRDefault="00E64EA3" w:rsidP="00E64EA3">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>Kamiyama Cove seemed to hold its breath, cradled in twilight’s embrace, while the secrets of Butterfly Heaven remained just that—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> just secrets</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>. For now.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0079EA47" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00B6302C" w:rsidRDefault="00B6302C" w:rsidP="00E237B0" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="799C9573" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E64EA3" w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3" w:rsidRDefault="00E64EA3" w:rsidP="00E64EA3">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>Night had settled back at the shrine by the time he returned, blanketing the old building in quiet serenity. The moon hung heavy and full, its silver light spilling across the stone paths and illuminating the delicate arches of the </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>Torii</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t> gate. Shadows stretched long and graceful over the gravel, like ink brushed onto parchment, silent and unyielding.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="071E5A23" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E64EA3" w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3" w:rsidRDefault="00E64EA3" w:rsidP="00E64EA3">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>In his office, a single lantern flickered, casting soft pools of amber light across the polished wooden floors. The warm glow danced along the grain of the wood, flickering like fireflies trapped in amber.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="32749FD9" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E64EA3" w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3" w:rsidRDefault="00E64EA3" w:rsidP="00E64EA3">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>Kōji sat cross-legged by the low wooden table, the remnants of a modest meal resting neatly on a lacquered tray beside him. Two tea cups stood empty, their rims still faintly scented with sencha. In the adjacent room, his mother, </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:b />
                <w:bCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>Kaede</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>, had long since drifted into sleep, her breaths soft and steady behind the thin walls.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3F2504F9" w14:textId="12EC4EF8" w:rsidR="00E64EA3" w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3" w:rsidRDefault="00E64EA3" w:rsidP="00E64EA3">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>Outside, the air was still, broken only by the occasional whisper of the wind through the </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>Keyaki</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">, its branches swaying gently as if whispering sweet nothings to </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>the </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>Sakura</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t> across the grove—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>a conversation held in rustling leaves and the sigh of the wind.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="45CC22B4" w14:textId="68CDDB72" w:rsidR="00B6302C" w:rsidRDefault="00E64EA3" w:rsidP="00B6302C">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>Kōji poured himself another cup of tea, the steam curling upwards like strands of incense smoke, delicate and unhurried. He leaned back with a sigh, letting the silence fold around him, the warmth of the cup settling into his palms. For a moment, he closed his eyes and simply listened—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>to the night, to the wind, to the old spirits that lingered just beyond the veil of sight.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4574C010" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00FD2628" w:rsidRPr="00FD2628" w:rsidRDefault="00FD2628" w:rsidP="00FD2628">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2628">
              <w:t>The shrill ring of the telephone sliced through the stillness, sharp and sudden, like a blade parting silk. Kōji’s eyes flickered to the corner of the room where the old receiver rested atop its cradle, dust gathered along its coiled cord like traces of forgotten conversations. He glanced towards the adjoining room, where his mother, mercifully deafened by age, slept soundly, untouched by the intrusion.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="2AF910F6" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00FD2628" w:rsidRPr="00FD2628" w:rsidRDefault="00FD2628" w:rsidP="00FD2628">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2628">
              <w:t>He set his cup down gently, the porcelain kissing the lacquered tray with a soft clink that seemed almost apologetic. Rising to his feet, he crossed the wooden floor with measured steps, the lantern’s glow casting his shadow long and thin against the shōji walls.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="42CFBBA4" w14:textId="0067A601" w:rsidR="00B6302C" w:rsidRDefault="00FD2628" w:rsidP="00B6302C">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2628">
              <w:t>His fingers wrapped around the receiver, lifting it with the familiarity of ritual. He brought it to his ear, the slight hum of the line humming through the silence. Kōji took a breath, steadying himself, and waited.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="5AD8DFE4" w14:textId="2358133C" w:rsidR="00B6302C" w:rsidRDefault="00B6302C" w:rsidP="00B6302C">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“Kōji,” came the familiar voice, distant but unmistakable. The static crackled softly in the line, the hum of the city filtering faintly through the receiver.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="47FC39F3" w14:textId="04E6B859" w:rsidR="00B6302C" w:rsidRDefault="00B6302C" w:rsidP="00B6302C">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“Saito,” Kōji replied, his tone warm, the syllables slipping from his lips like a breath of familiarity. “I didn’t expect another call so soon.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0C04DE68" w14:textId="3ACBBF15" w:rsidR="00B6302C" w:rsidRDefault="00B6302C" w:rsidP="00B6302C">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>A soft exhale of breath—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2628">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>relief, perhaps, or something more settled. “I just wanted to hear it… How did it go?”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4EB26241" w14:textId="6069C76D" w:rsidR="00B6302C" w:rsidRDefault="00B6302C" w:rsidP="00B6302C">
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">Kōji leaned back against the wooden frame, eyes drifting to the moonlit </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2628" w:rsidRPr="00FD2628">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>keidai</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2628" w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2628">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2628">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2628">
              <w:t>the shrine’s courtyard</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2628" w:rsidRPr="00E64EA3">
              <w:t>—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2628">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00FD2628" w:rsidRPr="00FD2628">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>outside. “It’s done. I placed the envelope by the entrance of Butterfly Heaven, just as you asked. The template’s in the mailbox. She’ll find it.” He paused, his gaze sharpening as he recalled the surreal image. “I saw her. In the garden.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="68A16FBD" w14:textId="55148BE5" w:rsidR="00B6302C" w:rsidRDefault="00B6302C" w:rsidP="00B6302C">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>A breath of silence. “You didn’t talk to her, did you?”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="14489E86" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00B6302C" w:rsidRDefault="00B6302C" w:rsidP="00B6302C">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>“No,” Kōji replied, his voice softening. “I didn’t say a word. She looked just like a spirit… it was so…” He hesitated, searching for the right word. “Unreal.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="40F62DA2" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00B6302C" w:rsidRDefault="00B6302C" w:rsidP="00B6302C" />
          <w:p w14:paraId="4B1D6D0C" w14:textId="1047AE3B" w:rsidR="00B6302C" w:rsidRDefault="00B6302C" w:rsidP="00B6302C">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>Saito’s voice came through the line, low and thoughtful. “She’s… not herself right now. She needs to find who she is before she can be seen.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4D9BD038" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00FD2628" w:rsidRDefault="00FD2628" w:rsidP="00B6302C">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00FD2628">
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>Kōji laughed, a rich, warm sound that filled the room with its sincerity. “And that’s why she was half-naked?” He chuckled again, shaking his head. “It was as if I’d stepped into one of those old ghost stories. A pale spirit flitting through the garden.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="70915B27" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00F91A8A" w:rsidRDefault="00F91A8A" w:rsidP="00B6302C">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t xml:space="preserve">There was a pause on the other end, a soft rustling of movement, and then Saito’s voice returned, softened by nostalgia. “You know how it is... the house brings things back to their essence. Maybe she’s just finding hers.” He chuckled, the sound carrying a touch of familiarity. “Or maybe it was just too hot? Kamiyama Cove summers are unforgiving.” </w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3E8AEA56" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00F91A8A" w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A" w:rsidRDefault="00F91A8A" w:rsidP="00F91A8A">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t>Kōji laughed, rich and full, the sound spilling into the stillness of the room. “Unforgiving?” he echoed, amusement colouring his voice. “Do you remember those summers by the creek? Swordfighting with bamboo stalks, the air so hot we had no clothes, just what we came to the world with?” His laugh deepened, rolling out in waves of genuine mirth. “If anyone had seen us back then, I imagine they’d have mistaken us for little forest spirits.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="040F2888" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00F91A8A" w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A" w:rsidRDefault="00F91A8A" w:rsidP="00F91A8A">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t>On the other end of the line, Saito chuckled, the warmth of memory threading through the static. “We would’ve given the </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>kitsune</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t> a run for their money,” he replied, his grin audible through the crackle of the line.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="6411B565" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00F91A8A" w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A" w:rsidRDefault="00F91A8A" w:rsidP="00F91A8A">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t>Kōji’s laughter faded into a smile, his eyes drifting to the moonlit keidai beyond the window. Shadows stretched across the stone paths, flickering under the soft glow of the lanterns. “Maybe we were,” he said softly, almost to himself. “Maybe we still are.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1668DA9B" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00F91A8A" w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A" w:rsidRDefault="00F91A8A" w:rsidP="00F91A8A">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t>He leaned back, taking a slow sip of his tea, the warmth settling into his bones. The smile lingered, softening the lines of his face. “I’m just amused!” he continued, his grin widening. “I’ve not had this much excitement in decades!”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4F9729E6" w14:textId="52C6C7BA" w:rsidR="00F91A8A" w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A" w:rsidRDefault="00F91A8A" w:rsidP="00F91A8A">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t>A pause hung in the air, stretching just long enough for memory to settle between them, gentle and unspoken. Then, almost unexpectedly, both men chuckled—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t>a low, familiar sound, carrying years of understanding and shared summers beneath the branches of the </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>Keyaki</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t> and the </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>Sakura</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t>.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="14CBB641" w14:textId="2EE90084" w:rsidR="00B6302C" w:rsidRDefault="00F91A8A" w:rsidP="00B6302C">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t>“Thank you, Kōji,” Saito murmured, his voice steady but threaded with something softer, something almost tender. “I’ll keep in touch.”</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="75B255CB" w14:textId="0BB96C9C" w:rsidR="00F91A8A" w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A" w:rsidRDefault="00F91A8A" w:rsidP="00F91A8A">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t>Kōji’s eyes drifted back to the window, where the bamboo swayed gently in the moonlight, shadows stretching long and delicate across the </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t>courtyard</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t>. “Please do, old friend,” he murmured, his voice softening, the words carrying the weight of trust that does not fade with time.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="226C431B" w14:textId="67F1A240" w:rsidR="00B6302C" w:rsidRDefault="00F91A8A" w:rsidP="00B6302C">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t>A faint click echoed through the receiver, sharp and final, and then there was only silence—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t>soft and unmoving, folding back around the shrine like the closing of a book. Outside, the wind whispered through the bamboo, carrying with it the echo of old memories.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="33A6476A" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00F91A8A" w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A" w:rsidRDefault="00F91A8A" w:rsidP="00F91A8A">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:lastRenderedPageBreak />
              <w:t>Kōji set the receiver down with a careful hand, the soft </w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>click</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F91A8A">
              <w:t> reverberating through the stillness. His gaze lingered on it for a moment longer, fingertips brushing the edge of the cradle as if tethered to the fading echoes of Saito's voice.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="0C265D0F" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="002C5345" w:rsidRPr="002C5345" w:rsidRDefault="002C5345" w:rsidP="002C5345">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002C5345">
              <w:t>He turned back to his cooling tea, the steam now barely visible, curling like distant memories. Outside, the wind whispered through the bamboo, stirring the stalks with a gentle sigh. It carried with it the faint scent of cedar, crisp and clean, mingling with the earthy musk of the grove—a breath of the forest that seemed to seep into the walls of the shrine itself.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="36CCAD9D" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="002C5345" w:rsidRPr="002C5345" w:rsidRDefault="002C5345" w:rsidP="002C5345">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002C5345">
              <w:t>Kōji inhaled slowly, the promise of secrets yet to be uncovered woven into the breeze, settling over the keidai like a veil. He took a sip, eyes drifting back to the moonlit path outside, and for a moment, it seemed as if the shadows themselves were moving, swaying with the rhythm of whispered prayers.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="652D3D78" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="002C5345" w:rsidRDefault="002C5345" w:rsidP="002C5345">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002C5345">
              <w:t>His fingers rested lightly on the rim of his cup, his gaze unfocused, distant. He closed his eyes, the warmth of memory unfurling like petals. Barely above a whisper, he murmured a soft prayer:</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="042AB596" w14:textId="79B6983F" w:rsidR="00770FC0" w:rsidRDefault="00770FC0" w:rsidP="002C5345">
            <w:r>
              <w:t>::tg::</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="45B3D021" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="001A3759" w:rsidRPr="001A3759" w:rsidRDefault="001A3759" w:rsidP="001A3759">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:spacing w:after="0" />
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="001A3759">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>空に舞う</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="1E4456E2" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="001A3759" w:rsidRPr="001A3759" w:rsidRDefault="001A3759" w:rsidP="001A3759">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:spacing w:after="0" />
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="001A3759">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>蝶の影を追い</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3EC5EE39" w14:textId="6004923E" w:rsidR="001A3759" w:rsidRDefault="001A3759" w:rsidP="001A3759">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:spacing w:after="0" />
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="001A3759">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>君は遠く</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00770FC0">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:br />
              <w:t>::/tg::</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="3E07CE21" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00F346BE" w:rsidRPr="001A3759" w:rsidRDefault="00F346BE" w:rsidP="001A3759">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:spacing w:after="0" />
              <w:rPr>
                <w:rFonts w:ascii="MS Gothic" w:eastAsia="MS Gothic" w:hAnsi="MS Gothic" w:cs="MS Gothic" />
                <w:lang w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="4F2DC2D2" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E42659" w:rsidRDefault="002C5345" w:rsidP="00E42659">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:spacing w:after="0" />
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F346BE">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t>Chasing shadows of</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00E42659">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="41BDC5CC" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E42659" w:rsidRDefault="002C5345" w:rsidP="00E42659">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:spacing w:after="0" />
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F346BE">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:br />
              <w:t>butterflies that dance in air—</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00E42659">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="65653880" w14:textId="2997DB1E" w:rsidR="002C5345" w:rsidRDefault="002C5345" w:rsidP="00E42659">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:spacing w:after="0" />
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="00F346BE">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:br />
              <w:t>you are far away.</w:t>
            </w:r>
            <w:r w:rsidR="00E42659">
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
              <w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="19214ABB" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="00E42659" w:rsidRPr="00F346BE" w:rsidRDefault="00E42659" w:rsidP="00E42659">
            <w:pPr>
              <w:spacing w:after="0" />
              <w:rPr>
                <w:i />
                <w:iCs />
              </w:rPr>
            </w:pPr>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="773566B4" w14:textId="77777777" w:rsidR="002C5345" w:rsidRPr="002C5345" w:rsidRDefault="002C5345" w:rsidP="002C5345">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002C5345">
              <w:t>He breathed out slowly, the ache of longing settling back into the quiet corners of his heart. "If you were here, Himiko… you would know how to mend her spirit. How will I guide this girl alone?"</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:p w14:paraId="5FABEC9C" w14:textId="5F667666" w:rsidR="00B6302C" w:rsidRPr="00E237B0" w:rsidRDefault="002C5345" w:rsidP="00F91A8A">
            <w:r w:rsidRPr="002C5345">
              <w:t>The words drifted into the stillness, caught in the sway of the bamboo, as if the grove itself held its breath.</w:t>
            </w:r>
          </w:p>
          <w:sectPr w:rsidR="00B6302C" w:rsidRPr="00E237B0">
            <w:pgSz w:w="11906" w:h="16838" />
            <w:pgMar w:top="1440" w:right="1440" w:bottom="1440" w:left="1440" w:header="708" w:footer="708" w:gutter="0" />
            <w:cols w:space="708" />
            <w:docGrid w:linePitch="360" />
          </w:sectPr>
        </w:body>
      </w:document>
    </pkg:xmlData>
  </pkg:part>
  <pkg:part pkg:name="/word/_rels/document.xml.rels" pkg:contentType="application/vnd.openxmlformats-package.relationships+xml" pkg:padding="256">
    <pkg:xmlData>
      <Relationships xmlns="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/package/2006/relationships">
        <Relationship Id="rId3" Type="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships/webSettings" Target="webSettings.xml" />
        <Relationship Id="rId2" Type="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships/settings" Target="settings.xml" />
        <Relationship Id="rId1" Type="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships/styles" Target="styles.xml" />
        <Relationship Id="rId5" Type="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships/theme" Target="theme/theme1.xml" />
        <Relationship Id="rId4" Type="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships/fontTable" Target="fontTable.xml" />
      </Relationships>
    </pkg:xmlData>
  </pkg:part>
  <pkg:part pkg:name="/word/theme/theme1.xml" pkg:contentType="application/vnd.openxmlformats-officedocument.theme+xml">
    <pkg:xmlData>
      <a:theme xmlns:a="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/main" name="Office Theme">
        <a:themeElements>
          <a:clrScheme name="Office">
            <a:dk1>
              <a:sysClr val="windowText" lastClr="000000" />
            </a:dk1>
            <a:lt1>
              <a:sysClr val="window" lastClr="FFFFFF" />
            </a:lt1>
            <a:dk2>
              <a:srgbClr val="0E2841" />
            </a:dk2>
            <a:lt2>
              <a:srgbClr val="E8E8E8" />
            </a:lt2>
            <a:accent1>
              <a:srgbClr val="156082" />
            </a:accent1>
            <a:accent2>
              <a:srgbClr val="E97132" />
            </a:accent2>
            <a:accent3>
              <a:srgbClr val="196B24" />
            </a:accent3>
            <a:accent4>
              <a:srgbClr val="0F9ED5" />
            </a:accent4>
            <a:accent5>
              <a:srgbClr val="A02B93" />
            </a:accent5>
            <a:accent6>
              <a:srgbClr val="4EA72E" />
            </a:accent6>
            <a:hlink>
              <a:srgbClr val="467886" />
            </a:hlink>
            <a:folHlink>
              <a:srgbClr val="96607D" />
            </a:folHlink>
          </a:clrScheme>
          <a:fontScheme name="Office">
            <a:majorFont>
              <a:latin typeface="Aptos Display" panose="02110004020202020204" />
              <a:ea typeface="" />
              <a:cs typeface="" />
              <a:font script="Jpan" typeface="游ゴシック Light" />
              <a:font script="Hang" typeface="맑은 고딕" />
              <a:font script="Hans" typeface="等线 Light" />
              <a:font script="Hant" typeface="新細明體" />
              <a:font script="Arab" typeface="Times New Roman" />
              <a:font script="Hebr" typeface="Times New Roman" />
              <a:font script="Thai" typeface="Angsana New" />
              <a:font script="Ethi" typeface="Nyala" />
              <a:font script="Beng" typeface="Vrinda" />
              <a:font script="Gujr" typeface="Shruti" />
              <a:font script="Khmr" typeface="MoolBoran" />
              <a:font script="Knda" typeface="Tunga" />
              <a:font script="Guru" typeface="Raavi" />
              <a:font script="Cans" typeface="Euphemia" />
              <a:font script="Cher" typeface="Plantagenet Cherokee" />
              <a:font script="Yiii" typeface="Microsoft Yi Baiti" />
              <a:font script="Tibt" typeface="Microsoft Himalaya" />
              <a:font script="Thaa" typeface="MV Boli" />
              <a:font script="Deva" typeface="Mangal" />
              <a:font script="Telu" typeface="Gautami" />
              <a:font script="Taml" typeface="Latha" />
              <a:font script="Syrc" typeface="Estrangelo Edessa" />
              <a:font script="Orya" typeface="Kalinga" />
              <a:font script="Mlym" typeface="Kartika" />
              <a:font script="Laoo" typeface="DokChampa" />
              <a:font script="Sinh" typeface="Iskoola Pota" />
              <a:font script="Mong" typeface="Mongolian Baiti" />
              <a:font script="Viet" typeface="Times New Roman" />
              <a:font script="Uigh" typeface="Microsoft Uighur" />
              <a:font script="Geor" typeface="Sylfaen" />
              <a:font script="Armn" typeface="Arial" />
              <a:font script="Bugi" typeface="Leelawadee UI" />
              <a:font script="Bopo" typeface="Microsoft JhengHei" />
              <a:font script="Java" typeface="Javanese Text" />
              <a:font script="Lisu" typeface="Segoe UI" />
              <a:font script="Mymr" typeface="Myanmar Text" />
              <a:font script="Nkoo" typeface="Ebrima" />
              <a:font script="Olck" typeface="Nirmala UI" />
              <a:font script="Osma" typeface="Ebrima" />
              <a:font script="Phag" typeface="Phagspa" />
              <a:font script="Syrn" typeface="Estrangelo Edessa" />
              <a:font script="Syrj" typeface="Estrangelo Edessa" />
              <a:font script="Syre" typeface="Estrangelo Edessa" />
              <a:font script="Sora" typeface="Nirmala UI" />
              <a:font script="Tale" typeface="Microsoft Tai Le" />
              <a:font script="Talu" typeface="Microsoft New Tai Lue" />
              <a:font script="Tfng" typeface="Ebrima" />
            </a:majorFont>
            <a:minorFont>
              <a:latin typeface="Aptos" panose="02110004020202020204" />
              <a:ea typeface="" />
              <a:cs typeface="" />
              <a:font script="Jpan" typeface="游明朝" />
              <a:font script="Hang" typeface="맑은 고딕" />
              <a:font script="Hans" typeface="等线" />
              <a:font script="Hant" typeface="新細明體" />
              <a:font script="Arab" typeface="Arial" />
              <a:font script="Hebr" typeface="Arial" />
              <a:font script="Thai" typeface="Cordia New" />
              <a:font script="Ethi" typeface="Nyala" />
              <a:font script="Beng" typeface="Vrinda" />
              <a:font script="Gujr" typeface="Shruti" />
              <a:font script="Khmr" typeface="DaunPenh" />
              <a:font script="Knda" typeface="Tunga" />
              <a:font script="Guru" typeface="Raavi" />
              <a:font script="Cans" typeface="Euphemia" />
              <a:font script="Cher" typeface="Plantagenet Cherokee" />
              <a:font script="Yiii" typeface="Microsoft Yi Baiti" />
              <a:font script="Tibt" typeface="Microsoft Himalaya" />
              <a:font script="Thaa" typeface="MV Boli" />
              <a:font script="Deva" typeface="Mangal" />
              <a:font script="Telu" typeface="Gautami" />
              <a:font script="Taml" typeface="Latha" />
              <a:font script="Syrc" typeface="Estrangelo Edessa" />
              <a:font script="Orya" typeface="Kalinga" />
              <a:font script="Mlym" typeface="Kartika" />
              <a:font script="Laoo" typeface="DokChampa" />
              <a:font script="Sinh" typeface="Iskoola Pota" />
              <a:font script="Mong" typeface="Mongolian Baiti" />
              <a:font script="Viet" typeface="Arial" />
              <a:font script="Uigh" typeface="Microsoft Uighur" />
              <a:font script="Geor" typeface="Sylfaen" />
              <a:font script="Armn" typeface="Arial" />
              <a:font script="Bugi" typeface="Leelawadee UI" />
              <a:font script="Bopo" typeface="Microsoft JhengHei" />
              <a:font script="Java" typeface="Javanese Text" />
              <a:font script="Lisu" typeface="Segoe UI" />
              <a:font script="Mymr" typeface="Myanmar Text" />
              <a:font script="Nkoo" typeface="Ebrima" />
              <a:font script="Olck" typeface="Nirmala UI" />
              <a:font script="Osma" typeface="Ebrima" />
              <a:font script="Phag" typeface="Phagspa" />
              <a:font script="Syrn" typeface="Estrangelo Edessa" />
              <a:font script="Syrj" typeface="Estrangelo Edessa" />
              <a:font script="Syre" typeface="Estrangelo Edessa" />
              <a:font script="Sora" typeface="Nirmala UI" />
              <a:font script="Tale" typeface="Microsoft Tai Le" />
              <a:font script="Talu" typeface="Microsoft New Tai Lue" />
              <a:font script="Tfng" typeface="Ebrima" />
            </a:minorFont>
          </a:fontScheme>
          <a:fmtScheme name="Office">
            <a:fillStyleLst>
              <a:solidFill>
                <a:schemeClr val="phClr" />
              </a:solidFill>
              <a:gradFill rotWithShape="1">
                <a:gsLst>
                  <a:gs pos="0">
                    <a:schemeClr val="phClr">
                      <a:lumMod val="110000" />
                      <a:satMod val="105000" />
                      <a:tint val="67000" />
                    </a:schemeClr>
                  </a:gs>
                  <a:gs pos="50000">
                    <a:schemeClr val="phClr">
                      <a:lumMod val="105000" />
                      <a:satMod val="103000" />
                      <a:tint val="73000" />
                    </a:schemeClr>
                  </a:gs>
                  <a:gs pos="100000">
                    <a:schemeClr val="phClr">
                      <a:lumMod val="105000" />
                      <a:satMod val="109000" />
                      <a:tint val="81000" />
                    </a:schemeClr>
                  </a:gs>
                </a:gsLst>
                <a:lin ang="5400000" scaled="0" />
              </a:gradFill>
              <a:gradFill rotWithShape="1">
                <a:gsLst>
                  <a:gs pos="0">
                    <a:schemeClr val="phClr">
                      <a:satMod val="103000" />
                      <a:lumMod val="102000" />
                      <a:tint val="94000" />
                    </a:schemeClr>
                  </a:gs>
                  <a:gs pos="50000">
                    <a:schemeClr val="phClr">
                      <a:satMod val="110000" />
                      <a:lumMod val="100000" />
                      <a:shade val="100000" />
                    </a:schemeClr>
                  </a:gs>
                  <a:gs pos="100000">
                    <a:schemeClr val="phClr">
                      <a:lumMod val="99000" />
                      <a:satMod val="120000" />
                      <a:shade val="78000" />
                    </a:schemeClr>
                  </a:gs>
                </a:gsLst>
                <a:lin ang="5400000" scaled="0" />
              </a:gradFill>
            </a:fillStyleLst>
            <a:lnStyleLst>
              <a:ln w="12700" cap="flat" cmpd="sng" algn="ctr">
                <a:solidFill>
                  <a:schemeClr val="phClr" />
                </a:solidFill>
                <a:prstDash val="solid" />
                <a:miter lim="800000" />
              </a:ln>
              <a:ln w="19050" cap="flat" cmpd="sng" algn="ctr">
                <a:solidFill>
                  <a:schemeClr val="phClr" />
                </a:solidFill>
                <a:prstDash val="solid" />
                <a:miter lim="800000" />
              </a:ln>
              <a:ln w="25400" cap="flat" cmpd="sng" algn="ctr">
                <a:solidFill>
                  <a:schemeClr val="phClr" />
                </a:solidFill>
                <a:prstDash val="solid" />
                <a:miter lim="800000" />
              </a:ln>
            </a:lnStyleLst>
            <a:effectStyleLst>
              <a:effectStyle>
                <a:effectLst />
              </a:effectStyle>
              <a:effectStyle>
                <a:effectLst />
              </a:effectStyle>
              <a:effectStyle>
                <a:effectLst>
                  <a:outerShdw blurRad="57150" dist="19050" dir="5400000" algn="ctr" rotWithShape="0">
                    <a:srgbClr val="000000">
                      <a:alpha val="63000" />
                    </a:srgbClr>
                  </a:outerShdw>
                </a:effectLst>
              </a:effectStyle>
            </a:effectStyleLst>
            <a:bgFillStyleLst>
              <a:solidFill>
                <a:schemeClr val="phClr" />
              </a:solidFill>
              <a:solidFill>
                <a:schemeClr val="phClr">
                  <a:tint val="95000" />
                  <a:satMod val="170000" />
                </a:schemeClr>
              </a:solidFill>
              <a:gradFill rotWithShape="1">
                <a:gsLst>
                  <a:gs pos="0">
                    <a:schemeClr val="phClr">
                      <a:tint val="93000" />
                      <a:satMod val="150000" />
                      <a:shade val="98000" />
                      <a:lumMod val="102000" />
                    </a:schemeClr>
                  </a:gs>
                  <a:gs pos="50000">
                    <a:schemeClr val="phClr">
                      <a:tint val="98000" />
                      <a:satMod val="130000" />
                      <a:shade val="90000" />
                      <a:lumMod val="103000" />
                    </a:schemeClr>
                  </a:gs>
                  <a:gs pos="100000">
                    <a:schemeClr val="phClr">
                      <a:shade val="63000" />
                      <a:satMod val="120000" />
                    </a:schemeClr>
                  </a:gs>
                </a:gsLst>
                <a:lin ang="5400000" scaled="0" />
              </a:gradFill>
            </a:bgFillStyleLst>
          </a:fmtScheme>
        </a:themeElements>
        <a:objectDefaults>
          <a:lnDef>
            <a:spPr />
            <a:bodyPr />
            <a:lstStyle />
            <a:style>
              <a:lnRef idx="2">
                <a:schemeClr val="accent1" />
              </a:lnRef>
              <a:fillRef idx="0">
                <a:schemeClr val="accent1" />
              </a:fillRef>
              <a:effectRef idx="1">
                <a:schemeClr val="accent1" />
              </a:effectRef>
              <a:fontRef idx="minor">
                <a:schemeClr val="tx1" />
              </a:fontRef>
            </a:style>
          </a:lnDef>
        </a:objectDefaults>
        <a:extraClrSchemeLst />
        <a:extLst>
          <a:ext uri="{05A4C25C-085E-4340-85A3-A5531E510DB2}">
            <thm15:themeFamily xmlns:thm15="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/thememl/2012/main" name="Office Theme" id="{2E142A2C-CD16-42D6-873A-C26D2A0506FA}" vid="{1BDDFF52-6CD6-40A5-AB3C-68EB2F1E4D0A}" />
          </a:ext>
        </a:extLst>
      </a:theme>
    </pkg:xmlData>
  </pkg:part>
  <pkg:part pkg:name="/word/settings.xml" pkg:contentType="application/vnd.openxmlformats-officedocument.wordprocessingml.settings+xml">
    <pkg:xmlData>
      <w:settings xmlns:mc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/markup-compatibility/2006" xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:m="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/math" xmlns:v="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:vml" xmlns:w10="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:word" xmlns:w="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main" xmlns:w14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordml" xmlns:w15="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2012/wordml" xmlns:w16cex="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2018/wordml/cex" xmlns:w16cid="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2016/wordml/cid" xmlns:w16="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2018/wordml" xmlns:w16du="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2023/wordml/word16du" xmlns:w16sdtdh="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2020/wordml/sdtdatahash" xmlns:w16sdtfl="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2024/wordml/sdtformatlock" xmlns:w16se="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2015/wordml/symex" xmlns:sl="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/schemaLibrary/2006/main" mc:Ignorable="w14 w15 w16se w16cid w16 w16cex w16sdtdh w16sdtfl w16du">
        <w:zoom w:percent="100" />
        <w:defaultTabStop w:val="720" />
        <w:characterSpacingControl w:val="doNotCompress" />
        <w:compat>
          <w:compatSetting w:name="compatibilityMode" w:uri="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word" w:val="15" />
          <w:compatSetting w:name="overrideTableStyleFontSizeAndJustification" w:uri="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word" w:val="1" />
          <w:compatSetting w:name="enableOpenTypeFeatures" w:uri="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word" w:val="1" />
          <w:compatSetting w:name="doNotFlipMirrorIndents" w:uri="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word" w:val="1" />
          <w:compatSetting w:name="differentiateMultirowTableHeaders" w:uri="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word" w:val="1" />
          <w:compatSetting w:name="useWord2013TrackBottomHyphenation" w:uri="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word" w:val="0" />
        </w:compat>
        <w:rsids>
          <w:rsidRoot w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00030501" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00124C5D" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00171C2E" />
          <w:rsid w:val="001A3759" />
          <w:rsid w:val="001B0E51" />
          <w:rsid w:val="002123DC" />
          <w:rsid w:val="002A1E3C" />
          <w:rsid w:val="002A6B6A" />
          <w:rsid w:val="002C5345" />
          <w:rsid w:val="002C6457" />
          <w:rsid w:val="002E2666" />
          <w:rsid w:val="002E4E9D" />
          <w:rsid w:val="002F7EDA" />
          <w:rsid w:val="0035762A" />
          <w:rsid w:val="003A60A5" />
          <w:rsid w:val="003A63D5" />
          <w:rsid w:val="003E5CAD" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00402C9E" />
          <w:rsid w:val="004056AF" />
          <w:rsid w:val="0045160E" />
          <w:rsid w:val="004F273F" />
          <w:rsid w:val="005347C6" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00565143" />
          <w:rsid w:val="005A1901" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00622F6E" />
          <w:rsid w:val="006F5000" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00741168" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00770FC0" />
          <w:rsid w:val="007B12AB" />
          <w:rsid w:val="007C710C" />
          <w:rsid w:val="008436FE" />
          <w:rsid w:val="008E6319" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00910F77" />
          <w:rsid w:val="009216CA" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00996C1D" />
          <w:rsid w:val="009C32C9" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00A315F8" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00A33EAD" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00A63347" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00A64A99" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00B6302C" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00B73C2D" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00C10E99" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00C446DE" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00C5653B" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00CB56B5" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00D34994" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00D77E08" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00DA407B" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00DD38B1" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E058E8" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E4086A" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E42659" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E60719" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E64EA3" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E712A6" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00F346BE" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00F91A8A" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00FD2628" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00FD2F58" />
        </w:rsids>
        <m:mathPr>
          <m:mathFont m:val="Cambria Math" />
          <m:brkBin m:val="before" />
          <m:brkBinSub m:val="--" />
          <m:smallFrac m:val="0" />
          <m:dispDef />
          <m:lMargin m:val="0" />
          <m:rMargin m:val="0" />
          <m:defJc m:val="centerGroup" />
          <m:wrapIndent m:val="1440" />
          <m:intLim m:val="subSup" />
          <m:naryLim m:val="undOvr" />
        </m:mathPr>
        <w:themeFontLang w:val="en-GB" w:eastAsia="ja-JP" />
        <w:clrSchemeMapping w:bg1="light1" w:t1="dark1" w:bg2="light2" w:t2="dark2" w:accent1="accent1" w:accent2="accent2" w:accent3="accent3" w:accent4="accent4" w:accent5="accent5" w:accent6="accent6" w:hyperlink="hyperlink" w:followedHyperlink="followedHyperlink" />
        <w:shapeDefaults>
          <o:shapedefaults v:ext="edit" spidmax="1026" />
          <o:shapelayout v:ext="edit">
            <o:idmap v:ext="edit" data="1" />
          </o:shapelayout>
        </w:shapeDefaults>
        <w:decimalSymbol w:val="." />
        <w:listSeparator w:val="," />
        <w14:docId w14:val="62B32535" />
        <w15:chartTrackingRefBased />
        <w15:docId w15:val="{5669A99F-B946-9340-A3D7-BB8ED8027999}" />
      </w:settings>
    </pkg:xmlData>
  </pkg:part>
  <pkg:part pkg:name="/word/styles.xml" pkg:contentType="application/vnd.openxmlformats-officedocument.wordprocessingml.styles+xml">
    <pkg:xmlData>
      <w:styles xmlns:mc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/markup-compatibility/2006" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:w="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main" xmlns:w14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordml" xmlns:w15="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2012/wordml" xmlns:w16cex="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2018/wordml/cex" xmlns:w16cid="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2016/wordml/cid" xmlns:w16="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2018/wordml" xmlns:w16du="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2023/wordml/word16du" xmlns:w16sdtdh="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2020/wordml/sdtdatahash" xmlns:w16sdtfl="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2024/wordml/sdtformatlock" xmlns:w16se="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2015/wordml/symex" mc:Ignorable="w14 w15 w16se w16cid w16 w16cex w16sdtdh w16sdtfl w16du">
        <w:docDefaults>
          <w:rPrDefault>
            <w:rPr>
              <w:rFonts w:asciiTheme="minorHAnsi" w:eastAsiaTheme="minorHAnsi" w:hAnsiTheme="minorHAnsi" w:cstheme="minorBidi" />
              <w:kern w:val="2" />
              <w:sz w:val="24" />
              <w:szCs w:val="24" />
              <w:lang w:val="en-GB" w:eastAsia="en-US" w:bidi="ar-SA" />
              <w14:ligatures w14:val="standardContextual" />
            </w:rPr>
          </w:rPrDefault>
          <w:pPrDefault>
            <w:pPr>
              <w:spacing w:after="160" w:line="278" w:lineRule="auto" />
            </w:pPr>
          </w:pPrDefault>
        </w:docDefaults>
        <w:latentStyles w:defLockedState="0" w:defUIPriority="99" w:defSemiHidden="0" w:defUnhideWhenUsed="0" w:defQFormat="0" w:count="376">
          <w:lsdException w:name="Normal" w:uiPriority="0" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="heading 1" w:uiPriority="9" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="heading 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="9" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="heading 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="9" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="heading 4" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="9" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="heading 5" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="9" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="heading 6" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="9" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="heading 7" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="9" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="heading 8" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="9" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="heading 9" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="9" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="index 1" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="index 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="index 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="index 4" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="index 5" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="index 6" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="index 7" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="index 8" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="index 9" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="toc 1" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="39" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="toc 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="39" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="toc 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="39" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="toc 4" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="39" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="toc 5" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="39" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="toc 6" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="39" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="toc 7" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="39" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="toc 8" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="39" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="toc 9" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="39" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Normal Indent" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="footnote text" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="annotation text" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="header" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="footer" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="index heading" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="caption" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="35" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="table of figures" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="envelope address" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="envelope return" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="footnote reference" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="annotation reference" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="line number" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="page number" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="endnote reference" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="endnote text" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="table of authorities" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="macro" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="toa heading" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Bullet" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Number" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List 4" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List 5" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Bullet 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Bullet 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Bullet 4" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Bullet 5" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Number 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Number 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Number 4" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Number 5" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Title" w:uiPriority="10" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Closing" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Signature" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Default Paragraph Font" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Body Text" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Body Text Indent" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Continue" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Continue 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Continue 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Continue 4" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Continue 5" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Message Header" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Subtitle" w:uiPriority="11" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Salutation" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Date" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Body Text First Indent" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Body Text First Indent 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Note Heading" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Body Text 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Body Text 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Body Text Indent 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Body Text Indent 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Block Text" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Hyperlink" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="FollowedHyperlink" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Strong" w:uiPriority="22" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Emphasis" w:uiPriority="20" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Document Map" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Plain Text" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="E-mail Signature" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="HTML Top of Form" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="HTML Bottom of Form" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Normal (Web)" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="HTML Acronym" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="HTML Address" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="HTML Cite" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="HTML Code" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="HTML Definition" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="HTML Keyboard" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="HTML Preformatted" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="HTML Sample" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="HTML Typewriter" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="HTML Variable" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Normal Table" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="annotation subject" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="No List" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Outline List 1" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Outline List 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Outline List 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Simple 1" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Simple 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Simple 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Classic 1" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Classic 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Classic 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Classic 4" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Colorful 1" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Colorful 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Colorful 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Columns 1" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Columns 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Columns 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Columns 4" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Columns 5" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Grid 1" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Grid 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Grid 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Grid 4" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Grid 5" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Grid 6" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Grid 7" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Grid 8" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table List 1" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table List 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table List 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table List 4" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table List 5" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table List 6" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table List 7" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table List 8" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table 3D effects 1" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table 3D effects 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table 3D effects 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Contemporary" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Elegant" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Professional" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Subtle 1" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Subtle 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Web 1" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Web 2" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Web 3" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Balloon Text" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Grid" w:uiPriority="39" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Table Theme" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Placeholder Text" w:semiHidden="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="No Spacing" w:uiPriority="1" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light Shading" w:uiPriority="60" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light List" w:uiPriority="61" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light Grid" w:uiPriority="62" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Shading 1" w:uiPriority="63" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Shading 2" w:uiPriority="64" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium List 1" w:uiPriority="65" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium List 2" w:uiPriority="66" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 1" w:uiPriority="67" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 2" w:uiPriority="68" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 3" w:uiPriority="69" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Dark List" w:uiPriority="70" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful Shading" w:uiPriority="71" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful List" w:uiPriority="72" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful Grid" w:uiPriority="73" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light Shading Accent 1" w:uiPriority="60" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light List Accent 1" w:uiPriority="61" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light Grid Accent 1" w:uiPriority="62" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Shading 1 Accent 1" w:uiPriority="63" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Shading 2 Accent 1" w:uiPriority="64" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium List 1 Accent 1" w:uiPriority="65" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Revision" w:semiHidden="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Paragraph" w:uiPriority="34" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Quote" w:uiPriority="29" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Intense Quote" w:uiPriority="30" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium List 2 Accent 1" w:uiPriority="66" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 1 Accent 1" w:uiPriority="67" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 2 Accent 1" w:uiPriority="68" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 3 Accent 1" w:uiPriority="69" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Dark List Accent 1" w:uiPriority="70" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful Shading Accent 1" w:uiPriority="71" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful List Accent 1" w:uiPriority="72" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful Grid Accent 1" w:uiPriority="73" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light Shading Accent 2" w:uiPriority="60" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light List Accent 2" w:uiPriority="61" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light Grid Accent 2" w:uiPriority="62" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Shading 1 Accent 2" w:uiPriority="63" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Shading 2 Accent 2" w:uiPriority="64" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium List 1 Accent 2" w:uiPriority="65" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium List 2 Accent 2" w:uiPriority="66" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 1 Accent 2" w:uiPriority="67" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 2 Accent 2" w:uiPriority="68" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 3 Accent 2" w:uiPriority="69" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Dark List Accent 2" w:uiPriority="70" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful Shading Accent 2" w:uiPriority="71" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful List Accent 2" w:uiPriority="72" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful Grid Accent 2" w:uiPriority="73" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light Shading Accent 3" w:uiPriority="60" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light List Accent 3" w:uiPriority="61" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light Grid Accent 3" w:uiPriority="62" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Shading 1 Accent 3" w:uiPriority="63" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Shading 2 Accent 3" w:uiPriority="64" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium List 1 Accent 3" w:uiPriority="65" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium List 2 Accent 3" w:uiPriority="66" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 1 Accent 3" w:uiPriority="67" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 2 Accent 3" w:uiPriority="68" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 3 Accent 3" w:uiPriority="69" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Dark List Accent 3" w:uiPriority="70" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful Shading Accent 3" w:uiPriority="71" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful List Accent 3" w:uiPriority="72" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful Grid Accent 3" w:uiPriority="73" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light Shading Accent 4" w:uiPriority="60" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light List Accent 4" w:uiPriority="61" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light Grid Accent 4" w:uiPriority="62" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Shading 1 Accent 4" w:uiPriority="63" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Shading 2 Accent 4" w:uiPriority="64" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium List 1 Accent 4" w:uiPriority="65" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium List 2 Accent 4" w:uiPriority="66" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 1 Accent 4" w:uiPriority="67" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 2 Accent 4" w:uiPriority="68" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 3 Accent 4" w:uiPriority="69" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Dark List Accent 4" w:uiPriority="70" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful Shading Accent 4" w:uiPriority="71" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful List Accent 4" w:uiPriority="72" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful Grid Accent 4" w:uiPriority="73" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light Shading Accent 5" w:uiPriority="60" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light List Accent 5" w:uiPriority="61" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light Grid Accent 5" w:uiPriority="62" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Shading 1 Accent 5" w:uiPriority="63" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Shading 2 Accent 5" w:uiPriority="64" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium List 1 Accent 5" w:uiPriority="65" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium List 2 Accent 5" w:uiPriority="66" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 1 Accent 5" w:uiPriority="67" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 2 Accent 5" w:uiPriority="68" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 3 Accent 5" w:uiPriority="69" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Dark List Accent 5" w:uiPriority="70" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful Shading Accent 5" w:uiPriority="71" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful List Accent 5" w:uiPriority="72" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful Grid Accent 5" w:uiPriority="73" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light Shading Accent 6" w:uiPriority="60" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light List Accent 6" w:uiPriority="61" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Light Grid Accent 6" w:uiPriority="62" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Shading 1 Accent 6" w:uiPriority="63" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Shading 2 Accent 6" w:uiPriority="64" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium List 1 Accent 6" w:uiPriority="65" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium List 2 Accent 6" w:uiPriority="66" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 1 Accent 6" w:uiPriority="67" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 2 Accent 6" w:uiPriority="68" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Medium Grid 3 Accent 6" w:uiPriority="69" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Dark List Accent 6" w:uiPriority="70" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful Shading Accent 6" w:uiPriority="71" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful List Accent 6" w:uiPriority="72" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Colorful Grid Accent 6" w:uiPriority="73" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Subtle Emphasis" w:uiPriority="19" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Intense Emphasis" w:uiPriority="21" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Subtle Reference" w:uiPriority="31" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Intense Reference" w:uiPriority="32" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Book Title" w:uiPriority="33" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Bibliography" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="37" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="TOC Heading" w:semiHidden="1" w:uiPriority="39" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" w:qFormat="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Plain Table 1" w:uiPriority="41" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Plain Table 2" w:uiPriority="42" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Plain Table 3" w:uiPriority="43" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Plain Table 4" w:uiPriority="44" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Plain Table 5" w:uiPriority="45" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table Light" w:uiPriority="40" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 1 Light" w:uiPriority="46" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 2" w:uiPriority="47" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 3" w:uiPriority="48" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 4" w:uiPriority="49" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 5 Dark" w:uiPriority="50" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 6 Colorful" w:uiPriority="51" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 7 Colorful" w:uiPriority="52" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 1 Light Accent 1" w:uiPriority="46" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 2 Accent 1" w:uiPriority="47" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 3 Accent 1" w:uiPriority="48" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 4 Accent 1" w:uiPriority="49" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 5 Dark Accent 1" w:uiPriority="50" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 6 Colorful Accent 1" w:uiPriority="51" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 7 Colorful Accent 1" w:uiPriority="52" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 1 Light Accent 2" w:uiPriority="46" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 2 Accent 2" w:uiPriority="47" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 3 Accent 2" w:uiPriority="48" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 4 Accent 2" w:uiPriority="49" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 5 Dark Accent 2" w:uiPriority="50" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 6 Colorful Accent 2" w:uiPriority="51" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 7 Colorful Accent 2" w:uiPriority="52" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 1 Light Accent 3" w:uiPriority="46" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 2 Accent 3" w:uiPriority="47" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 3 Accent 3" w:uiPriority="48" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 4 Accent 3" w:uiPriority="49" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 5 Dark Accent 3" w:uiPriority="50" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 6 Colorful Accent 3" w:uiPriority="51" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 7 Colorful Accent 3" w:uiPriority="52" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 1 Light Accent 4" w:uiPriority="46" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 2 Accent 4" w:uiPriority="47" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 3 Accent 4" w:uiPriority="48" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 4 Accent 4" w:uiPriority="49" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 5 Dark Accent 4" w:uiPriority="50" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 6 Colorful Accent 4" w:uiPriority="51" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 7 Colorful Accent 4" w:uiPriority="52" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 1 Light Accent 5" w:uiPriority="46" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 2 Accent 5" w:uiPriority="47" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 3 Accent 5" w:uiPriority="48" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 4 Accent 5" w:uiPriority="49" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 5 Dark Accent 5" w:uiPriority="50" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 6 Colorful Accent 5" w:uiPriority="51" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 7 Colorful Accent 5" w:uiPriority="52" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 1 Light Accent 6" w:uiPriority="46" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 2 Accent 6" w:uiPriority="47" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 3 Accent 6" w:uiPriority="48" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 4 Accent 6" w:uiPriority="49" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 5 Dark Accent 6" w:uiPriority="50" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 6 Colorful Accent 6" w:uiPriority="51" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Grid Table 7 Colorful Accent 6" w:uiPriority="52" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 1 Light" w:uiPriority="46" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 2" w:uiPriority="47" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 3" w:uiPriority="48" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 4" w:uiPriority="49" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 5 Dark" w:uiPriority="50" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 6 Colorful" w:uiPriority="51" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 7 Colorful" w:uiPriority="52" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 1 Light Accent 1" w:uiPriority="46" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 2 Accent 1" w:uiPriority="47" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 3 Accent 1" w:uiPriority="48" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 4 Accent 1" w:uiPriority="49" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 5 Dark Accent 1" w:uiPriority="50" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 6 Colorful Accent 1" w:uiPriority="51" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 7 Colorful Accent 1" w:uiPriority="52" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 1 Light Accent 2" w:uiPriority="46" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 2 Accent 2" w:uiPriority="47" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 3 Accent 2" w:uiPriority="48" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 4 Accent 2" w:uiPriority="49" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 5 Dark Accent 2" w:uiPriority="50" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 6 Colorful Accent 2" w:uiPriority="51" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 7 Colorful Accent 2" w:uiPriority="52" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 1 Light Accent 3" w:uiPriority="46" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 2 Accent 3" w:uiPriority="47" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 3 Accent 3" w:uiPriority="48" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 4 Accent 3" w:uiPriority="49" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 5 Dark Accent 3" w:uiPriority="50" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 6 Colorful Accent 3" w:uiPriority="51" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 7 Colorful Accent 3" w:uiPriority="52" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 1 Light Accent 4" w:uiPriority="46" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 2 Accent 4" w:uiPriority="47" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 3 Accent 4" w:uiPriority="48" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 4 Accent 4" w:uiPriority="49" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 5 Dark Accent 4" w:uiPriority="50" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 6 Colorful Accent 4" w:uiPriority="51" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 7 Colorful Accent 4" w:uiPriority="52" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 1 Light Accent 5" w:uiPriority="46" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 2 Accent 5" w:uiPriority="47" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 3 Accent 5" w:uiPriority="48" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 4 Accent 5" w:uiPriority="49" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 5 Dark Accent 5" w:uiPriority="50" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 6 Colorful Accent 5" w:uiPriority="51" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 7 Colorful Accent 5" w:uiPriority="52" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 1 Light Accent 6" w:uiPriority="46" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 2 Accent 6" w:uiPriority="47" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 3 Accent 6" w:uiPriority="48" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 4 Accent 6" w:uiPriority="49" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 5 Dark Accent 6" w:uiPriority="50" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 6 Colorful Accent 6" w:uiPriority="51" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="List Table 7 Colorful Accent 6" w:uiPriority="52" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Mention" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Smart Hyperlink" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Hashtag" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Unresolved Mention" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
          <w:lsdException w:name="Smart Link" w:semiHidden="1" w:unhideWhenUsed="1" />
        </w:latentStyles>
        <w:style w:type="paragraph" w:default="1" w:styleId="Normal">
          <w:name w:val="Normal" />
          <w:qFormat />
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="paragraph" w:styleId="Heading1">
          <w:name w:val="heading 1" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="Normal" />
          <w:next w:val="Normal" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading1Char" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:pPr>
            <w:keepNext />
            <w:keepLines />
            <w:spacing w:before="360" w:after="80" />
            <w:outlineLvl w:val="0" />
          </w:pPr>
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:asciiTheme="majorHAnsi" w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:hAnsiTheme="majorHAnsi" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:color w:val="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
            <w:sz w:val="40" />
            <w:szCs w:val="40" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="paragraph" w:styleId="Heading2">
          <w:name w:val="heading 2" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="Normal" />
          <w:next w:val="Normal" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading2Char" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:unhideWhenUsed />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:pPr>
            <w:keepNext />
            <w:keepLines />
            <w:spacing w:before="160" w:after="80" />
            <w:outlineLvl w:val="1" />
          </w:pPr>
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:asciiTheme="majorHAnsi" w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:hAnsiTheme="majorHAnsi" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:color w:val="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
            <w:sz w:val="32" />
            <w:szCs w:val="32" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="paragraph" w:styleId="Heading3">
          <w:name w:val="heading 3" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="Normal" />
          <w:next w:val="Normal" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading3Char" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:unhideWhenUsed />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:pPr>
            <w:keepNext />
            <w:keepLines />
            <w:spacing w:before="160" w:after="80" />
            <w:outlineLvl w:val="2" />
          </w:pPr>
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:color w:val="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
            <w:sz w:val="28" />
            <w:szCs w:val="28" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="paragraph" w:styleId="Heading4">
          <w:name w:val="heading 4" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="Normal" />
          <w:next w:val="Normal" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading4Char" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:unhideWhenUsed />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:pPr>
            <w:keepNext />
            <w:keepLines />
            <w:spacing w:before="80" w:after="40" />
            <w:outlineLvl w:val="3" />
          </w:pPr>
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:i />
            <w:iCs />
            <w:color w:val="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="paragraph" w:styleId="Heading5">
          <w:name w:val="heading 5" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="Normal" />
          <w:next w:val="Normal" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading5Char" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:unhideWhenUsed />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:pPr>
            <w:keepNext />
            <w:keepLines />
            <w:spacing w:before="80" w:after="40" />
            <w:outlineLvl w:val="4" />
          </w:pPr>
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:color w:val="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="paragraph" w:styleId="Heading6">
          <w:name w:val="heading 6" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="Normal" />
          <w:next w:val="Normal" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading6Char" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:unhideWhenUsed />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:pPr>
            <w:keepNext />
            <w:keepLines />
            <w:spacing w:before="40" w:after="0" />
            <w:outlineLvl w:val="5" />
          </w:pPr>
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:i />
            <w:iCs />
            <w:color w:val="595959" w:themeColor="text1" w:themeTint="A6" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="paragraph" w:styleId="Heading7">
          <w:name w:val="heading 7" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="Normal" />
          <w:next w:val="Normal" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading7Char" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:unhideWhenUsed />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:pPr>
            <w:keepNext />
            <w:keepLines />
            <w:spacing w:before="40" w:after="0" />
            <w:outlineLvl w:val="6" />
          </w:pPr>
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:color w:val="595959" w:themeColor="text1" w:themeTint="A6" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="paragraph" w:styleId="Heading8">
          <w:name w:val="heading 8" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="Normal" />
          <w:next w:val="Normal" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading8Char" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:unhideWhenUsed />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:pPr>
            <w:keepNext />
            <w:keepLines />
            <w:spacing w:after="0" />
            <w:outlineLvl w:val="7" />
          </w:pPr>
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:i />
            <w:iCs />
            <w:color w:val="272727" w:themeColor="text1" w:themeTint="D8" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="paragraph" w:styleId="Heading9">
          <w:name w:val="heading 9" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="Normal" />
          <w:next w:val="Normal" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading9Char" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:unhideWhenUsed />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:pPr>
            <w:keepNext />
            <w:keepLines />
            <w:spacing w:after="0" />
            <w:outlineLvl w:val="8" />
          </w:pPr>
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:color w:val="272727" w:themeColor="text1" w:themeTint="D8" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:default="1" w:styleId="DefaultParagraphFont">
          <w:name w:val="Default Paragraph Font" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="1" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:unhideWhenUsed />
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="table" w:default="1" w:styleId="TableNormal">
          <w:name w:val="Normal Table" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="99" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:unhideWhenUsed />
          <w:tblPr>
            <w:tblInd w:w="0" w:type="dxa" />
            <w:tblCellMar>
              <w:top w:w="0" w:type="dxa" />
              <w:left w:w="108" w:type="dxa" />
              <w:bottom w:w="0" w:type="dxa" />
              <w:right w:w="108" w:type="dxa" />
            </w:tblCellMar>
          </w:tblPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="numbering" w:default="1" w:styleId="NoList">
          <w:name w:val="No List" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="99" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:unhideWhenUsed />
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:customStyle="1" w:styleId="Heading1Char">
          <w:name w:val="Heading 1 Char" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="DefaultParagraphFont" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading1" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:asciiTheme="majorHAnsi" w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:hAnsiTheme="majorHAnsi" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:color w:val="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
            <w:sz w:val="40" />
            <w:szCs w:val="40" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:customStyle="1" w:styleId="Heading2Char">
          <w:name w:val="Heading 2 Char" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="DefaultParagraphFont" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading2" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:asciiTheme="majorHAnsi" w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:hAnsiTheme="majorHAnsi" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:color w:val="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
            <w:sz w:val="32" />
            <w:szCs w:val="32" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:customStyle="1" w:styleId="Heading3Char">
          <w:name w:val="Heading 3 Char" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="DefaultParagraphFont" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading3" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:color w:val="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
            <w:sz w:val="28" />
            <w:szCs w:val="28" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:customStyle="1" w:styleId="Heading4Char">
          <w:name w:val="Heading 4 Char" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="DefaultParagraphFont" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading4" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:i />
            <w:iCs />
            <w:color w:val="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:customStyle="1" w:styleId="Heading5Char">
          <w:name w:val="Heading 5 Char" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="DefaultParagraphFont" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading5" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:color w:val="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:customStyle="1" w:styleId="Heading6Char">
          <w:name w:val="Heading 6 Char" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="DefaultParagraphFont" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading6" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:i />
            <w:iCs />
            <w:color w:val="595959" w:themeColor="text1" w:themeTint="A6" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:customStyle="1" w:styleId="Heading7Char">
          <w:name w:val="Heading 7 Char" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="DefaultParagraphFont" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading7" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:color w:val="595959" w:themeColor="text1" w:themeTint="A6" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:customStyle="1" w:styleId="Heading8Char">
          <w:name w:val="Heading 8 Char" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="DefaultParagraphFont" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading8" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:i />
            <w:iCs />
            <w:color w:val="272727" w:themeColor="text1" w:themeTint="D8" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:customStyle="1" w:styleId="Heading9Char">
          <w:name w:val="Heading 9 Char" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="DefaultParagraphFont" />
          <w:link w:val="Heading9" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="9" />
          <w:semiHidden />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:color w:val="272727" w:themeColor="text1" w:themeTint="D8" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="paragraph" w:styleId="Title">
          <w:name w:val="Title" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="Normal" />
          <w:next w:val="Normal" />
          <w:link w:val="TitleChar" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="10" />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:pPr>
            <w:spacing w:after="80" w:line="240" w:lineRule="auto" />
            <w:contextualSpacing />
          </w:pPr>
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:asciiTheme="majorHAnsi" w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:hAnsiTheme="majorHAnsi" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:spacing w:val="-10" />
            <w:kern w:val="28" />
            <w:sz w:val="56" />
            <w:szCs w:val="56" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:customStyle="1" w:styleId="TitleChar">
          <w:name w:val="Title Char" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="DefaultParagraphFont" />
          <w:link w:val="Title" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="10" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:asciiTheme="majorHAnsi" w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:hAnsiTheme="majorHAnsi" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:spacing w:val="-10" />
            <w:kern w:val="28" />
            <w:sz w:val="56" />
            <w:szCs w:val="56" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="paragraph" w:styleId="Subtitle">
          <w:name w:val="Subtitle" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="Normal" />
          <w:next w:val="Normal" />
          <w:link w:val="SubtitleChar" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="11" />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:pPr>
            <w:numPr>
              <w:ilvl w:val="1" />
            </w:numPr>
          </w:pPr>
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:color w:val="595959" w:themeColor="text1" w:themeTint="A6" />
            <w:spacing w:val="15" />
            <w:sz w:val="28" />
            <w:szCs w:val="28" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:customStyle="1" w:styleId="SubtitleChar">
          <w:name w:val="Subtitle Char" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="DefaultParagraphFont" />
          <w:link w:val="Subtitle" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="11" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rPr>
            <w:rFonts w:eastAsiaTheme="majorEastAsia" w:cstheme="majorBidi" />
            <w:color w:val="595959" w:themeColor="text1" w:themeTint="A6" />
            <w:spacing w:val="15" />
            <w:sz w:val="28" />
            <w:szCs w:val="28" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="paragraph" w:styleId="Quote">
          <w:name w:val="Quote" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="Normal" />
          <w:next w:val="Normal" />
          <w:link w:val="QuoteChar" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="29" />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:pPr>
            <w:spacing w:before="160" />
            <w:jc w:val="center" />
          </w:pPr>
          <w:rPr>
            <w:i />
            <w:iCs />
            <w:color w:val="404040" w:themeColor="text1" w:themeTint="BF" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:customStyle="1" w:styleId="QuoteChar">
          <w:name w:val="Quote Char" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="DefaultParagraphFont" />
          <w:link w:val="Quote" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="29" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rPr>
            <w:i />
            <w:iCs />
            <w:color w:val="404040" w:themeColor="text1" w:themeTint="BF" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="paragraph" w:styleId="ListParagraph">
          <w:name w:val="List Paragraph" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="Normal" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="34" />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:pPr>
            <w:ind w:left="720" />
            <w:contextualSpacing />
          </w:pPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:styleId="IntenseEmphasis">
          <w:name w:val="Intense Emphasis" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="DefaultParagraphFont" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="21" />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rPr>
            <w:i />
            <w:iCs />
            <w:color w:val="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="paragraph" w:styleId="IntenseQuote">
          <w:name w:val="Intense Quote" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="Normal" />
          <w:next w:val="Normal" />
          <w:link w:val="IntenseQuoteChar" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="30" />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:pPr>
            <w:pBdr>
              <w:top w:val="single" w:sz="4" w:space="10" w:color="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
              <w:bottom w:val="single" w:sz="4" w:space="10" w:color="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
            </w:pBdr>
            <w:spacing w:before="360" w:after="360" />
            <w:ind w:left="864" w:right="864" />
            <w:jc w:val="center" />
          </w:pPr>
          <w:rPr>
            <w:i />
            <w:iCs />
            <w:color w:val="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:customStyle="1" w:styleId="IntenseQuoteChar">
          <w:name w:val="Intense Quote Char" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="DefaultParagraphFont" />
          <w:link w:val="IntenseQuote" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="30" />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rPr>
            <w:i />
            <w:iCs />
            <w:color w:val="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
        <w:style w:type="character" w:styleId="IntenseReference">
          <w:name w:val="Intense Reference" />
          <w:basedOn w:val="DefaultParagraphFont" />
          <w:uiPriority w:val="32" />
          <w:qFormat />
          <w:rsid w:val="00E237B0" />
          <w:rPr>
            <w:b />
            <w:bCs />
            <w:smallCaps />
            <w:color w:val="0F4761" w:themeColor="accent1" w:themeShade="BF" />
            <w:spacing w:val="5" />
          </w:rPr>
        </w:style>
      </w:styles>
    </pkg:xmlData>
  </pkg:part>
  <pkg:part pkg:name="/word/webSettings.xml" pkg:contentType="application/vnd.openxmlformats-officedocument.wordprocessingml.webSettings+xml">
    <pkg:xmlData>
      <w:webSettings xmlns:mc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/markup-compatibility/2006" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:w="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main" xmlns:w14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordml" xmlns:w15="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2012/wordml" xmlns:w16cex="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2018/wordml/cex" xmlns:w16cid="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2016/wordml/cid" xmlns:w16="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2018/wordml" xmlns:w16du="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2023/wordml/word16du" xmlns:w16sdtdh="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2020/wordml/sdtdatahash" xmlns:w16sdtfl="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2024/wordml/sdtformatlock" xmlns:w16se="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2015/wordml/symex" mc:Ignorable="w14 w15 w16se w16cid w16 w16cex w16sdtdh w16sdtfl w16du">
        <w:divs>
          <w:div w:id="20329054">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="52047738">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="135680726">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="152256493">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="247008658">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="249043155">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="375786596">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="388574807">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="472522447">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="529950106">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="612056778">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="629365939">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="688793392">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="692148664">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="779842259">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="920993333">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="1028260320">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="1055928237">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="1322468731">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="1363050206">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="1477992702">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="1718703159">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="1757095178">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="1792046858">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="2040273854">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
          <w:div w:id="2060130346">
            <w:bodyDiv w:val="1" />
            <w:marLeft w:val="0" />
            <w:marRight w:val="0" />
            <w:marTop w:val="0" />
            <w:marBottom w:val="0" />
            <w:divBdr>
              <w:top w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:left w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:bottom w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
              <w:right w:val="none" w:sz="0" w:space="0" w:color="auto" />
            </w:divBdr>
          </w:div>
        </w:divs>
        <w:optimizeForBrowser />
        <w:allowPNG />
      </w:webSettings>
    </pkg:xmlData>
  </pkg:part>
  <pkg:part pkg:name="/word/fontTable.xml" pkg:contentType="application/vnd.openxmlformats-officedocument.wordprocessingml.fontTable+xml">
    <pkg:xmlData>
      <w:fonts xmlns:mc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/markup-compatibility/2006" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:w="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main" xmlns:w14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordml" xmlns:w15="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2012/wordml" xmlns:w16cex="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2018/wordml/cex" xmlns:w16cid="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2016/wordml/cid" xmlns:w16="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2018/wordml" xmlns:w16du="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2023/wordml/word16du" xmlns:w16sdtdh="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2020/wordml/sdtdatahash" xmlns:w16sdtfl="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2024/wordml/sdtformatlock" xmlns:w16se="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2015/wordml/symex" mc:Ignorable="w14 w15 w16se w16cid w16 w16cex w16sdtdh w16sdtfl w16du">
        <w:font w:name="Aptos">
          <w:charset w:val="00" />
          <w:family w:val="swiss" />
          <w:pitch w:val="variable" />
          <w:sig w:usb0="20000287" w:usb1="00000003" w:usb2="00000000" w:usb3="00000000" w:csb0="0000019F" w:csb1="00000000" />
        </w:font>
        <w:font w:name="Times New Roman">
          <w:panose1 w:val="02020603050405020304" />
          <w:charset w:val="00" />
          <w:family w:val="roman" />
          <w:pitch w:val="variable" />
          <w:sig w:usb0="E0002EFF" w:usb1="C000785B" w:usb2="00000009" w:usb3="00000000" w:csb0="000001FF" w:csb1="00000000" />
        </w:font>
        <w:font w:name="Aptos Display">
          <w:charset w:val="00" />
          <w:family w:val="swiss" />
          <w:pitch w:val="variable" />
          <w:sig w:usb0="20000287" w:usb1="00000003" w:usb2="00000000" w:usb3="00000000" w:csb0="0000019F" w:csb1="00000000" />
        </w:font>
        <w:font w:name="Yu Gothic Light">
          <w:altName w:val="游ゴシック Light" />
          <w:panose1 w:val="020B0300000000000000" />
          <w:charset w:val="80" />
          <w:family w:val="swiss" />
          <w:pitch w:val="variable" />
          <w:sig w:usb0="E00002FF" w:usb1="2AC7FDFF" w:usb2="00000016" w:usb3="00000000" w:csb0="0002009F" w:csb1="00000000" />
        </w:font>
        <w:font w:name="MS Gothic">
          <w:altName w:val="ＭＳ ゴシック" />
          <w:panose1 w:val="020B0609070205080204" />
          <w:charset w:val="80" />
          <w:family w:val="modern" />
          <w:pitch w:val="fixed" />
          <w:sig w:usb0="E00002FF" w:usb1="6AC7FDFB" w:usb2="08000012" w:usb3="00000000" w:csb0="0002009F" w:csb1="00000000" />
        </w:font>
        <w:font w:name="Yu Mincho">
          <w:altName w:val="游明朝" />
          <w:panose1 w:val="02020400000000000000" />
          <w:charset w:val="80" />
          <w:family w:val="roman" />
          <w:pitch w:val="variable" />
          <w:sig w:usb0="800002E7" w:usb1="2AC7FCFF" w:usb2="00000012" w:usb3="00000000" w:csb0="0002009F" w:csb1="00000000" />
        </w:font>
      </w:fonts>
    </pkg:xmlData>
  </pkg:part>
  <pkg:part pkg:name="/docProps/core.xml" pkg:contentType="application/vnd.openxmlformats-package.core-properties+xml" pkg:padding="256">
    <pkg:xmlData>
      <cp:coreProperties xmlns:cp="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/package/2006/metadata/core-properties" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:dcmitype="http://purl.org/dc/dcmitype/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
        <dc:title />
        <dc:subject />
        <dc:creator>Javier Cuervos</dc:creator>
        <cp:keywords />
        <dc:description />
        <cp:lastModifiedBy>Javier Cuervos</cp:lastModifiedBy>
        <cp:revision>5</cp:revision>
        <dcterms:created xsi:type="dcterms:W3CDTF">2025-05-18T20:53:00Z</dcterms:created>
        <dcterms:modified xsi:type="dcterms:W3CDTF">2025-05-19T10:11:00Z</dcterms:modified>
      </cp:coreProperties>
    </pkg:xmlData>
  </pkg:part>
  <pkg:part pkg:name="/docProps/app.xml" pkg:contentType="application/vnd.openxmlformats-officedocument.extended-properties+xml" pkg:padding="256">
    <pkg:xmlData>
      <Properties xmlns="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/extended-properties" xmlns:vt="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/docPropsVTypes">
        <Template>Normal.dotm</Template>
        <TotalTime>4</TotalTime>
        <Pages>27</Pages>
        <Words>9764</Words>
        <Characters>55658</Characters>
        <Application>Microsoft Office Word</Application>
        <DocSecurity>0</DocSecurity>
        <Lines>463</Lines>
        <Paragraphs>130</Paragraphs>
        <ScaleCrop>false</ScaleCrop>
        <HeadingPairs>
          <vt:vector size="2" baseType="variant">
            <vt:variant>
              <vt:lpstr>Title</vt:lpstr>
            </vt:variant>
            <vt:variant>
              <vt:i4>1</vt:i4>
            </vt:variant>
          </vt:vector>
        </HeadingPairs>
        <TitlesOfParts>
          <vt:vector size="1" baseType="lpstr">
            <vt:lpstr />
          </vt:vector>
        </TitlesOfParts>
        <Company />
        <LinksUpToDate>false</LinksUpToDate>
        <CharactersWithSpaces>65292</CharactersWithSpaces>
        <SharedDoc>false</SharedDoc>
        <HyperlinksChanged>false</HyperlinksChanged>
        <AppVersion>16.0000</AppVersion>
      </Properties>
    </pkg:xmlData>
  </pkg:part>
</pkg:package>
